我们怎么知道他不在洛杉矶？
How do we know he's not in Los Angeles?
我们承诺
We were promised,
如你所知 电话会在4:00来到我们
as you know, the call would come to us at 4:00.
现在是4:00后10分钟
It's now 10 minutes after 4:00.
我们在洛杉矶等待 打电话
We're waiting here, in Los Angeles, for a phone call
从传说中的亿万富翁 霍华德休斯
from legendary billionaire, Howard Hughes,
这可以debunk ...
which could debunk...
我们在洛杉矶等待 打电话
We're waiting here, in Los Angeles, for a phone call
从传说中的亿万富翁 霍华德休斯
from legendary billionaire, Howard Hughes,
这可能会破坏作家的声称他写的
which could debunk a writer's claim that he's written
Hughes的授权自传
an authorized autobiography of Hughes,
并且休斯处于永久性的痴呆状态
and that Hughes is in a permanent state of dementia.
霍华德休斯
The location of Howard Hughes,
仍然是一个完整的奥秘给我们
still a complete mystery to us.
如果他不能打电话
And if he's unable to call,
正如休斯组织所承诺的
as promised by the Hughes organization,
并证明他是有坚定的头脑
and prove that he is of sound mind,
好的 组织的国防合同
well, the organization's defense contracts,
其医疗基础
its medical foundation,
甚至其赌场牌照也可能受到威胁
even its casino licenses could be in jeopardy.
如果他不叫承诺
If he doesn't call as promised,
他会很难为自己辩护
it's gonna be hard for him to defend himself
反对在米斯金的书中的指控
against the charges in Miskin's book.
是的 无论他在哪里
Yes, wherever he's hiding.
是的 我现在告诉我们 我们只能等待
Yes, I'm told now that we can only wait
为休斯先生打电话直到4:30
for Mr. Hughes' phone call until 4:30.
很少私人公民
Very few private citizens
可以说是已经发展起来的
can be said to have developed
这样惊人的影响力
such an astounding amount of influence,
名人和成就
celebrity and achievement.
总是关注新的人才
Always with an eye out for new talent,
休斯发展了声誉
Hughes developed a reputation
雇用几十个年轻 有抱负的女演员
for employing dozens of young, aspiring actresses,
并保持合同
and keeping them under contract
...多年来在RKO
...for years at RKO,
不管是否
regardless of whether or not
他们曾经出现在他的一张照片中
they ever appear in one of his pictures.
你好？
Hello?
霍华德•休斯曾经是美国的理想
Howard Hughes was once the American ideal.
电影制片人 飞行员 发明家...
A moviemaker, an aviator, an inventor...
霍华德？
Howard?
...和一个工业家 谁 18岁
...and an industrialist, who, at the age of 18,
继承了给他一个垄断的财富
inherited a fortune which gave him a monopoly
在世界上最好的设备上
on the best device in the world
用于钻油
with which to drill for oil.
这是一个有关系的人
This is a man with relationships
与总统 军事领导人和人民...
with presidents, military leaders and people who are...
霍华德 你剩下18分钟才能打电话
Howard, you've got 18 minutes left to place the call.
在1930年 他制作了最昂贵的电影有史以来
In 1930, he produced the most expensive movie ever made.
好吧 Miskin的书说
Well, Miskin's book says
霍华德•休斯不记得什么了
that Howard Hughes cannot remember anything,
他完全无法沟通
that he's completely unable to communicate.
那么 尽管他无数的飞机坠毁
Well, despite his countless plane crashes,
所有的他生存...
all of which he survived...
霍华德 你能听到我吗？
Howard, can you hear me?
他的设计在他自己的赛车飞机上设置了新的速度记录
His design set new speed records in his own racing aircraft,
他本质上成了一个美国的英雄
and he essentially became an American hero.
当然 他是一个美国英雄
Of course, he's an American hero.
但它不像是
But it's not as if
他不能犯错误
he's incapable of making a mistake.
他可以在制作过程中
He could be in the middle of making
现在有一个很大的错误
a big mistake right now.
我想你错了 休斯先生
I think you're mistaken, Mr. Hughes.
我想你错了
I think you're mistaken.
我不犯错误 上校
I don't make mistakes, Colonel.
好吧 他不犯错误
Okay, he doesn't make mistakes.
国防部已经安排你的航班...
The Department of Defense has scheduled your flight...
国防部没有发明这架飞机 上校
The Department of Defense didn't invent this plane, Colonel.
我做了 我付了
I did. I paid for it,
我会登陆它 当我没有准备好登陆！
and I'll land it when I'm goddamn ready to land it!
你正在拿起苹果花女王
You are picking up the Apple Blossom Queen.
她的名字是Marla Mabrey
Her name is Marla Mabrey.
去那里 得到她
Go down there, get her,
并驱使她直接到她的房子
and drive her straight to her house.
记住 任何司机谁尝试任何一个汗衫
Remember, any driver who tries any hanky-panky
与合同女演员走了
with a contract actress is gone.
他被解雇了
He's fired.
谢谢
Thank you.
Mabrey小姐 我是Frank 很高兴见到你
Miss Mabrey, I'm Frank. Nice to meet you.
祝贺你是苹果花女王
Congratulations on being the Apple Blossom Queen.
车就在那边 我会得到 呃...
The car's just over there. I'll get the, uh...
我是卢赛 弗兰克 我是Marla的母亲
I'm Lucey, Frank. I'm Marla's mother.
哦
Oh.
- 呃... - 这是Marla
- Uh... - This is Marla.
- 嗨 我是弗兰克 - 嗨
- Hi, I'm Frank. - Hi.
呃 这边 请
Uh, this way, please.
哦...
Oh...
- 实在抱歉 - 好的 好吧
- Sorry, sorry. - Okay. All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
让我给你
Let me get that for you.
- 谢谢 - 当然
- Thank you. - Of course.
Marla真的很兴奋 她真的
Marla's so excited that she's actually
终于会见霍华德休斯
gonna finally meet Howard Hughes.
今天会发生吗？
Will that be happening today?
这对我很难说 女士
That's hard for me to say, ma'am.
我是新的工作
I'm new on the job.
我只是 两个星期前我从弗雷斯诺来到这里
I just, I got here from Fresno two weeks ago.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
两个星期在洛杉矶
Two weeks in Los Angeles
你在为霍华德休斯工作？
and you're working for Howard Hughes?
没有伤害有很高的希望 女士
No harm having high hopes, ma'am.
你去什么教会 弗兰克
And what church do you go to, Frank,
如果你不介意我的要求？
if you don't mind my asking?
好吧 这是第一卫理公会 它在弗雷斯诺
Well, it's First Methodist. It's in Fresno.
哦 好的 你是卫理公会
Oh. All right, you're a Methodist.
- 对 - 我原谅你
- Right. - I forgive you.
- 哦 她在开玩笑 - 我们是浸礼者
- Oh. She's kidding. - We're Baptists.
有福的救主！
Blessed savior!
哦 我的天啊！ 多么美妙的风景！
Oh, my goodness! What a view!
这是非常 非常好 这是...
This is very, very nice. This is...
在世界上是从哪里来的？
Where in the world is that coming from?
那是那里的好莱坞碗
That's the Hollywood Bowl down there.
我想他们正在排练
I think they're rehearsing.
真？
Really?
每周400美元呢？
$400 a week on top of this?
你父亲从来没有见过每周400美元
And your father never saw $400 a week
甚至作为正教授
even as a full professor.
嗯 袋子都在楼上 厨房里放养
Um, the bags are all upstairs. The kitchen's stocked.
呃 我会在...
Uh, I'll be right in the...
外面在车里 如果你需要我
Outside in the car, if you need me.
你知道最近的施洗派教会在哪里吗？
Do you know where the nearest Baptist church would be?
我马上检查一下 女士
I'll check on that right away, ma'am.
所以它只是似乎不可能
So it just doesn't seem likely
我们今天下午会见休斯先生吗？
that we'll meet Mr. Hughes this afternoon?
我们假设我们一到达就会见他
We assumed we'd meet him as soon as we arrived.
斯特拉星光的脚本在哪里？
And where is the script for Stella Starlight?
哦 对不起 我不...
Oh, I'm sorry, I don't...
任何想法 当我做屏幕测试？
Any idea when I do the screen test?
对不起 我真的...
I'm sorry, I really...
对不起 对不起
Excuse me, sorry.
呃 我会在车外的
Uh, I'll be right outside in the car
直到你的下一个驱动程序开始
until your next driver comes on.
他的名字是Levar
His name is Levar.
哦 我的星星！
Oh, my stars!
为什么这些椅子这么远？
Why are these chairs so far back?
我要把它们移开
I'm gonna move them up.
艾森豪威尔总统
President Eisenhower
接着说政府
went on to say that the government
有他所说的
has what he termed,
“在书架上的各种有用的项目
"all sorts of useful projects on the shelf,"
实施行动
to be put into action
反对经济衰退 如果和需要的话
against the recession if and when they're needed.
这个国家的经济
The economy of this country
是比很多更强
is a lot stronger than
我看到的那些人的精神...
the spirit of those people that I see...
“求你祝福我们 哦 主啊 因为这些 你的恩赐
"Bless us, oh, Lord, for these, Thy gifts
“我们将要从你的赏金
"that we are about to receive from thy bounty,
“通过基督 我们的主
"through Christ, Our Lord.
- “阿门 - 阿门
- "Amen." - Amen.
好吧 从我所有的阅读关于霍华德休斯
Well, from all I've read about Howard Hughes
我希望他不期望在一些酒店房间见到你
I hope he doesn't expect to meet you in some hotel room.
嗨
Hi.
♪金星如果你♪
♪ Venus if you will ♪
♪请给一个小女孩 我的快感♪
♪ Please send a little girl for me to thrill ♪
♪谁想要我的吻和我怀里的女孩♪
♪ A girl who wants my kisses and my arms ♪
♪一个女孩与你所有的魅力♪
♪ A girl with all the charms of you ♪
♪金星 让她公平♪
♪ Venus, make her fair ♪
♪一个可爱女孩 她的头发太阳光♪
♪ A lovely girl with sunlight in her hair ♪
所以 你有鱼子酱吗？
So, did you get caviar?
是的 我有鱼子酱 但我还没有见到他
Yes, I got caviar but I still haven't met him.
你有什么想法有多少房子
Do you have any idea how many houses
他有合同下的女演员吗？
he has for actresses under contract?
我觉得像14
I think something like 14.
更像22
More like 22.
更像26
More like 26.
- 二十六？ - 二十六？
- Twenty six? - Twenty six?
这是我们如何得到报酬？
This is how we get paid?
天上的主！
Lord in heaven!
纳丁 我今天会见休斯先生吗？
Nadine, am I meeting Mr. Hughes today?
坐
Sit.
这是一个工程问题
This is an engineering problem.
你知道这些是什么吗？
You do know what these are?
是飞机的这些船体吗？
Are these hulls of an aircraft?
什么？
What?
我不知道 双浮筒？
I don't know. Twin pontoons?
我们做电影 霍华德
We do movies, Howard.
我们不知道浮筒 螺旋桨...
We don't know pontoons, propellers...
先生们
Gentlemen,
衣服围绕乳房的方式
the way that the dress fits around the breasts
使它看起来像他们填充
makes it look like they're padded.
如果胸罩在乳头上包含某种点
If the brassiere incorporated some kind of point at the nipple
它会解决这个问题
it would solve that.
并尽量不让罗素小姐
And try not to let Miss Russell
听到你叫他们浮桥
hear you call them pontoons.
下午好 先生们
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
两个女孩都要去周末
Both girls are going away for the weekend,
所以现在去
so go now.
哦 弗兰克 你在那里
Oh, Frank, there you are.
听着 你在膨胀
Listen, you're doing swell,
我想让你准备开车的老板任何分钟
and I want you to be prepared to drive the boss any minute.
好吧 我妈妈去世了
Well, my mom passed away.
其实 我主要是由我的奶奶养育
Actually, I was raised mostly by my grandma.
和你的爸爸？
And your dad?
呃...
Uh...
好吧 他 那种 在她去世之前起飞了 所以...
Well, he, kind of, took off before she passed away, so...
我想每隔几个星期
I think every few weeks,
我可能会回去
I'll probably be able to go back
看到我的奶奶和我的女孩
and see my grandma and my girl.
我从街上长大
I grew up across the street from,
其实 我的未婚妻
actually, my fiancée.
现在她照顾她父亲的狗狗窝
Right now she takes care of her father's dog kennel.
你认为我会见到休斯先生吗？
Do you think I'll ever get to meet Mr. Hughes?
所以 是谁说的...
So, who was it that said...
“他们还服务谁只等待”？
"They also serve who only stand and wait"?
约翰•米尔顿对他的失明
John Milton on his blindness.
对你好 聪明的cookie
Good for you, smart cookie.
你知道 他们在好莱坞说
You know, they say in Hollywood,
一个女孩可以遇到麻烦
a girl can get in trouble
具有智能的情况
for having a case of the smarts.
不只是在好莱坞 亲爱的
Not just in Hollywood, honey.
哈哈
Ha-ha.
但如果你或我做一个动作
But if you or me make a move
在这些小鸡之一 我们死在水中
on one of these chicks, we are dead in the water.
我们是历史 我们被解雇了
We're history. We're fired.
铁娘子出现了
And the Iron Maiden has emerged.
- 什么？ - 铁娘子
- The what? - Iron Maiden.
处女玛拉
The virgin Marla.
你做了吗？ 那太糟了
You did? That's horrible.
停下 你
Stop, you.
这是怎么回事？ 我打电话给你三次
What's going on? I called you three times.
请 我迟到了我的4:00
Please, I'm late for my 4:00.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
你害怕老人会听到
You afraid the old man will hear
你和一个正常的家伙说话？
you were talking to a normal guy?
哦 请 不
Oh, please, no.
只是不要 不要这样做
Just don't, don't do this.
我不做什么 也不是你
I'm not doing anything and neither are you.
你不允许做...
You're not allowed to do...
我做的很好 谢谢
I'm doing just fine. Thank you.
你知道吗？ 算了吧
You know what? Forget it.
这是什么？
What was that about?
有些人从不停止寻找隐藏萨拉米香肠
Some guys never stop looking to hide the salami.
什么？
What?
- 什么？ - 隐藏萨拉米香肠
- What? - Hide the salami.
做行动
Do the deed.
浸泡灯芯
Dip the wick.
油漆手杖
Varnish the cane.
黄油松饼
Butter the muffin.
我知道了
I get it.
再见 女孩
Bye, girls.
♪他岩树顶整天♪
♪ He rocks in the tree tops all day long ♪
♪霍'和A - boppin'和-唱他的歌曲♪
♪ Hoppin' and a-boppin' and a-singing his song ♪
♪所有在Jaybird街♪小鸟
♪ All the little birds on Jaybird Street ♪
♪喜欢听到知更鸟的鸣叫去 鸣叫 鸣叫♪
♪ Love to hear the robin go tweet, tweet, tweet ♪
♪摇滚罗宾♪
♪ Rockin' robin ♪
♪鸣叫 鸣叫 鸣叫♪
♪ Tweet, tweet, tweet ♪
♪摇滚罗宾♪
♪ Rockin' robin ♪
♪鸣叫 琴声-李-迪♪
♪ Tweet, tweedle-lee-dee ♪
♪去摇滚罗宾♪
♪ Go rockin' robin ♪
♪“因为我们是真的 今晚要摇滚♪
♪ 'Cause we're really gonna rock tonight ♪
妈妈告诉我 六个月前
Mam ie told me that six months ago
其中一个司机被解雇了
one of the drivers got fired
因为他和她一起吃晚饭
because he ate dinner with her.
但Sally说所有的驱动程序
But Sally says all the drivers
必须通过他们的教会雇用
have to be hired through their churches.
好 这不会使他们的天使
Fine, that doesn't make them angels.
弗兰克•福布斯的未婚妻什么时候来到城里 反正呢？
And when is Frank Forbes' fiancée coming to town, anyway?
♪我不想跳弹浪漫♪
♪ I don't want a ricochet romance ♪
♪我不想跳弹爱♪
♪ I don't want a ricochet love ♪
♪如果你不小心用你的吻♪
♪ If you're careless with your kisses ♪
♪找到另一斑鸠♪
♪ Find another turtle dove ♪
♪我不想跳弹浪漫♪
♪ I don't want a ricochet romance ♪
♪不 不 不是我♪
♪ No, no, not me ♪
♪如果你要去跳弹 宝宝♪
♪ If you're gonna ricochet, baby ♪
♪我要你重获自由♪
♪ I'm gonna set you free ♪
对福布斯而言 不要对电池充电
Reverend Forbes, do not charge the battery,
如果你不打算使用灯
if you're not going to use the lights.
除非 当然 你想被解雇
Unless, of course, you'd like to be fired.
无论如何 处女玛拉的浸礼会
Anyway, the virgin Marla's a Baptist.
你知道为什么浸礼会教徒认为他妈的坏 不是吗？
You do know why Baptists think fucking is bad, don't you?
因为它可能会导致跳舞
Because it might lead to dancing.
把它关掉 Levar
Knock it off, Levar.
♪马 他冲我挤眉弄眼......♪
♪ Ma, he's making eyes at me... ♪
这是这个
And here's this.
哦谢谢
Oh, thank you.
小心 奶奶
Careful, Granny.
“因为食物和你所有的爱的礼物
"For food and all thy gifts of love,
“我们给你的感谢和赞美
"we give Thee thanks and praise.
“从下面俯视 哦 耶稣
"Look down, oh, Jesus, from above
“祝福我们所有的日子
"and bless us all our days."
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
很高兴你现在感觉好些了 布兰斯福德先生
Glad you're feeling better now, Mr. Bransford.
你的未婚妻一直在做
Your fiancée's been doing
一个鲸鱼的工作与狗窝 弗兰克
a whale of a job with the kennel, Frank.
但小狗都告诉我他们在这里想念你
But the puppies all tell me they miss you around here.
你找到我们的房子至少有一个小院子？
Will the house you find us have at least a tiny yard?
绝对
Absolutely.
你还是觉得
And you still feel
霍华德•休斯将有兴趣
Howard Hughes is going to be interested
在发展住房项目
in developing a housing project
与你的年龄的孩子？
with a kid your age?
当你终于见到他
When you finally meet him.
因为众人都犯了罪 没有上帝的荣耀
For all have sinned and come short of the glory of God.
圣经说 我们都是罪人
The Bible says that we're all sinners.
而“罪”这个词实际上是指
And the word "sin" actually means
我们已经缺少了
that we've come short of
上帝的标准
God's standards.
耶稣说...
Jesus said...
...我们应该爱主的上帝
...that we should love the Lord God
与我们的心 心灵和灵魂
with all our heart, mind, and soul
和我们的邻居自己 我想如果...
and our neighbors ourselves. And I think if...
你认为他知道吗？
You think he knows?
知道什么？
Knows what?
你知道 你和我有...
You know, that you and I have...
...走了一路
...gone all the way.
不要愚蠢
Don't be silly.
弗兰克 你为什么所有的司机都会放慢脚步
Frank, why do all you drivers slow down
并再次加速这样？
and speed up again like that?
这些是来自休斯组织
These are from the Hughes organization.
请读卡4
Read card 4, please.
阅读4
Read 4.
“当运送女性合同球员时
"When transporting female contract players,
“司机每小时将减速到两英里
"drivers will slow to two miles per hour
“任何洼地 洼地 起伏或障碍
"at any dip, swale, undulation or impediment
“可能会挤压不支持的身体部位
"that may jostle unsupported body parts."
这是什么意思 身体部位？
What does that mean, body parts?
你在开玩笑！
You're kidding!
我甚至没有见到他 他在保护我的身体部位？
I haven't even met him and he's protecting my body parts?
- 这是什么意思？ - 妈妈 他的意思是我的...
- What does it mean? - Mom, he means my...
哦 我的上帝 这太可怕了！
Oh, my God. That's outrageous!
我知道 他怎么知道他们不受支持？
I know. How does he know they're unsupported?
- 这不是有趣的 马拉！ - 这就是我想知道的
- It's not amusing, Marla! - That's what I wanna know.
这很有趣
It's funny.
这不是有点有趣
It's not in the slightest bit amusing.
对待这些女人喜欢他拥有自己的身体
To treat these women like he owns their bodies.
- 他没有自己的身体 - 让这些年轻女孩上课
- He doesn't own their bodies. - To have these young girls go to class
在他们的小小的舞蹈服装
in their tiny little dance outfits.
制服 他们叫制服
Uniforms, they're called uniforms.
让他们抓住他们的薪水
Have them grabbing for their paychecks
就像是一个钩子上的诱饵
like it was bait on a hook.
- 它是什么 - 求您了 妈妈
- Which it is. - Mom, please.
这只是这样的侮ing和不尊重
It's just so insulting and disrespectful.
你只是看这一切
And you just watch all this
没有说一个字
without saying one word,
- 弗兰克 不是一个单词 - 他要说什么？
- Frank, not a single word. - What's he going to say?
Mabrey夫人 我签了合同
Mrs. Mabrey, I've signed a contract
同意不谈论休斯先生
agreeing not to talk about Mr. Hughes.
哦 有吗？ 我只能想象
Oh, have you? I can only imagine
什么是你不会谈论的
what it is you won't talk about.
你知道我女儿从来没有见过休斯先生吗？
Do you realize my daughter's never met Mr. Hughes?
我 女士
I do, ma'am.
从来没有听说过关于这个屏幕测试的一个字？
Never heard one word from him about this screen test?
你知道 你已经救了你的钱
You know, you've saved your money.
你是一个聪明的女孩
You're a smart girl.
你可以买到很多鱼子酱在皇家 弗吉尼亚州 亲爱的
You can buy a lot of caviar back in Front Royal, Virginia, my dear.
他们没有鱼子酱
They don't have caviar
回到前面皇家 弗吉尼亚 亲爱的
back in Front Royal, Virginia, my dear.
不要和我小姐 小姐
Don't you be snippy with me, young lady.
没有人会更年轻
Nobody's getting any younger.
Mabrey夫人 我很感谢你们保持我们之间
Mrs. Mabrey, I'd appreciate your keeping this between us.
我从来没有见过休斯先生
I've never met Mr. Hughes either.
- 阿门 - 阿门
- Amen. - Amen.
我会得到它
I'll get it.
你好？
Hello?
- Mabrey？ - 是的 Nadine
- Mabrey? - Yes, Nadine.
房子里的一切都很好？
Everything in the house is fine?
是的 一切都很好
Yes, everything is fine.
谢谢 我们想知道
Thank you. We would like to know,
什么时候是Stella Starlight的屏幕测试？
when is the screen test for Stella Starlight?
而在天堂的地方 是霍华德•休斯先生
And where, for heaven's sake, is Mr. Howard Hughes
谁从来没有足够的
who's never been gracious enough
她一直在这里对我的女儿说一个字？
to speak one word to my daughter since she's been here?
我们不是几个弗吉尼亚州坎普金斯
We are not a couple of Virginia bumpkins.
我们等了足够久了
We've waited long enough.
我没有什么可以说 晚安
I have nothing further to say. Good night.
Marla
Marla,
你拒绝了奖学金给玛丽华盛顿
you turned down a scholarship to Mary Washington.
你从来没有写过一首歌
You haven't written a song since you've been here,
你甚至没有遇到这个人
and you haven't even met this man
谁应该让你的屏幕测试
who's supposedly making your screen test.
他的钱不够买你的时间
His money is not enough to buy your time.
妈妈 他是好莱坞的国王
Mom, he's the king of Hollywood,
他是美国最受人尊敬的人之一
he's one of the most respected men in America.
他是一个天才
He's some kind of a genius.
每个人都想要他 他是一个忙碌的人
Everybody wants him, he's a busy man.
你是一个有天赋的年轻女子 有美好的未来
And you are a gifted young woman with a wonderful future.
上帝禁止 在这样的城镇
God forbid, in a town like this.
这个游戏霍华德休斯戏剧与年轻女性
This game Howard Hughes plays with young women,
它不会骗我一个位
it doesn't fool me one bit.
没有人会更年轻
Nobody's getting any younger.
我们要回家
We are going home.
我们？
We?
我爱你妈妈
I love you, Mom.
我会帮你包
I'll help you pack.
圣经告诉我们
The Bible tells us,
无论谁看着一个女人
that whosoever looketh on a woman
到她后欲望
to lust after her,
与她已经在他的心里犯了通奸
hath committed adultery with her already in his heart.
有人告诉我们圣经
Someone who tells us the Bible
在婚前不处理性别
doesn't deal with sex before marriage
只是试图避免感到内疚
is simply trying to avoid feeling guilty.
有一个时间收获和一个时间播种
There is a time to reap and a time to sow.
有一个时间拥抱
There is a time to embrace,
和时间避免拥抱
and a time to refrain from embracing.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
教会怎么样？
How was church?
想念你的妈妈 是吗？
Miss your mom, huh?
让我们走吧 我喜欢开车
Let's just go. I like driving.
我不认为你知道如何
I didn't think you knew how.
啊! 我的意思是 我喜欢去驾驶
Ugh! I mean, I like going for a drive.
我知道如何驾驶 或我做 我们走吧
I know how to drive, or I did. Let's go.
你是什么意思？
What do you mean "You did"?
我的爸爸 神安息他的灵魂
My dad, God rest his soul,
认为女司机是危险的
thought women drivers were dangerous,
所以我退出 然后我忘了怎么样 好的？
so I quit, then I forgot how. Okay?
- 你在做什么？ - 你会记得
- What are you doing? - You'll remember.
你有驾驶执照 不是吗？
You've got a driver's license, don't you?
我们走吧 我想给你一个地方Mulholland Drive
Let's go. I want to show you a place off Mulholland Drive.
等待
Wait.
这是很好的回到这里
It's nice back here.
嘿!
Hey!
噢
Ooh.
哦
Oh.
想告诉我什么？
What do wanna show me?
这只是一些我想开发的面积
It's just some acreage I wanna develop.
在这里慢一点
Slow down a little bit around here.
这是为经济适用房
It's for affordable housing.
负担得起的房子？
Affordable housing?
是啊 你知道 那些不富有的人
Yeah. You know, people who aren't rich.
他们想离开城市
They wanna get out of the cities,
并进入郊区
and into the suburbs.
只是走一个权利 在这里 拿一个权利 在这里？
Just take a right, right here. Take a right, right here?
没关系
Never mind.
我要给你看的地方 Teamsters拥有它
The land I'm gonna show you, the Teamsters own it.
他们试图把它做成一个高尔夫球场
They tried making it a golf course,
但没有人来
but nobody came.
好吧 你可以减慢一点点 对吧？
Okay, you can slow down a little bit more, right?
这是117英亩
It's 117 acres.
我觉得 你知道 如果你做一个很好的交易
I feel, you know, if you make a good deal
在土地上 然后你细分...
on the land and then you subdivide...
我不是指大房子
I don't mean big houses,
我的意思是 中产阶级家庭的温和房子
I mean, modest houses for middle class families.
好吧 有...
Okay, there's...
现在是王权
Cash is king right now.
以霍华德•休斯作为支持者
With Howard Hughes as a backer,
我的意思是 我知道我可以让他获利
I mean, I know I can make him a profit.
我想叫它Mulholland峡谷
I wanna call it Mulholland Canyon.
你有光
You got a light.
他们再次告诉我 “准备开车上司
They told me again, "Be ready to drive the boss."
哇！ 你甚至可以见到那个家伙
Wow! You might even meet the guy.
我应该成为司机
I should become a driver.
好 我开车
Well, I'm driving.
我认为你对这个地方是对的
I think you're right about this place.
他们早些时候告诉我
They told me earlier,
类被取消 他们没有打电话给你？
class was canceled. They didn't call you?
我从来不知道发生了什么
I never quite know what's going on.
我有一个奇怪的日子
I had such a strange day.
我在Schwab的外面
I was outside at Schwab's,
这个家伙开始和我说话
and this guy started talking to me.
这是很好 我的意思是他不是...
It was nice, I mean he wasn't...
他没有在我或任何东西
He wasn't making a pass at me or anything,
但我们谈了 他说
but we talked, and he said
他想吃晚饭 我是...
he'd like to have dinner, and I'm...
我只是看着他
I'm just looking at him,
然后我意识到我在说什么
and then I realize who I'm talking to.
鲍比•达林
Bobby Darin.
我说 “我不敢相信
I said, "I can't believe it.
“你是鲍比•达林
"You're Bobby Darin."
我的意思是 好吧 他不知道我是一个演员或什么
I mean, okay, he didn't know I was an actress or anything.
但我甚至不知道他是鲍比•达林
But I didn't even know he was Bobby Darin.
它只是...
It just...
一世...
I...
我觉得...
I feel...
旧
Old.
旧？
Old?
我的意思是 你不会在好莱坞作为一个规则
I mean, wouldn't you say in Hollywood as a rule,
当你一直在这里只要我有
when you've been here as long as I have
你应该已经或多或少
that you should have already more or less
显示你可以做什么？
shown what you can do?
让我们老实说 也许我不是这个的正确的女孩
Let's be honest, maybe I'm not the right girl for this,
我的意思是 你不应该有大的怀抱
I mean aren't you supposed to have big bosoms
和性感和休闲的一切？
and be sexy and casual about everything?
我是一个广场
I'm a square.
我真的不能行动 我不能跳舞
I can't really act. I can't dance.
我可以写歌 但我不能真正唱
I can write songs, but I can't really sing.
电影女演员应该唱歌 而不是写歌
A movie actress should sing songs, not write them.
你不会说这是真的吗？
Wouldn't you say that's true?
我的意思是 作为一条规则
I mean, as a rule.
我的意思是 在这个城镇 不是那些规则？
I mean, in this town, aren't those the rules?
什么？
What?
来吧 弗兰克 你知道规则
Come on, Frank, you know the rules.
你是个例外
You're an exception.
这些规则不适用于您
The rules don't apply to you.
等一下
Hold on.
你好？
Hello?
Marla hi
Marla, hi.
我只是想让你知道...
I just wanted you to know...
你今晚会见休斯先生
you're meeting with Mr. Hughes tonight.
我会派人立即接你
I'll send someone to pick you up right away.
谢谢
Thank you.
你猜怎么了
Guess what.
这是比佛利山庄酒店？
This is the Beverly Hills Hotel?
我们带着Polo休息室的私人入口
We take the private entrance to the Polo Lounge.
嗨！
Hi!
哦谢谢
Oh, thank you.
哦
Oh.
你想喝鸡尾酒吗？
Would you like a cocktail?
哦...
Oh...
我不喝酒
I don't drink.
- 好吧 我会在车里 - 哦好的
- Okay, I'll be in the car. - Oh, okay.
你会跟我来 Mabrey女士吗？
Would you follow me, Ms. Mabrey?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
- 这里是黑暗的 - 有座位
- It's dark in here. - Have a seat.
他总是保持这黑暗吗？
Does he always keep it this dark?
他住在这个平房吗？
Does he stay in this bungalow?
对不起 我不能说
Sorry, I can't say.
我听说他有五个平房吗？
Did I hear he has five bungalows?
嗯
Hmm.
这些瓶子里有什么？
What's in those bottles?
那是水
That's water.
从缅因
From Maine.
水
Water.
从缅因
From Maine.
弗兰克还在这里吗？
Is Frank still here?
他是 呃...
He's, uh...
他在车里
He's in the car.
你喜欢填字游戏？
You like crossword puzzles?
是啊
Yeah.
是？
Yes?
马上
Right away.
啊! 休斯先生 我从你的图片认出你
Ah! Mr. Hughes. I recognize you from your pictures.
我要感谢你
I'd like to thank you.
感谢您对我的表演班
Thank you for my acting classes,
谢谢你对我的芭蕾课
thank you for my ballet classes,
感谢你的房子
thank you for the house
谢谢你的薪水
thank you for the paycheck,
并感谢您的机会成为明星
and thank you for the chance to become a star.
你的名字 是...
Your name is, is...
- 玛拉 - 玛拉
- Marla. - Marla.
- 玛拉马布里 - 玛拉马布里是
- Marla Mabrey. - Marla Mabrey. Yes.
一些香槟 玛拉？
Some champagne, Marla?
不好了 不 谢谢 我不喝酒
Oh, no. No, thank you, I don't drink.
你不喜欢喝酒？
You don't like to have a drink?
不 实际上我从来没有过的
No, actually I've never had one.
你从来没有喝过酒？
You've never had a drink?
没有
No.
嗯
Huh.
你从来没有在你的生命喝一杯吗？
You've never had a drink in your life?
没有
No.
好样的 对你有好处
Good for you, good for you.
你吃了 是吗？
You do eat, yes?
我做
I do.
是的 我做好吃的
Yes, I do eat.
啊 啧啧
Ah, gee.
这是整洁 牛排 土豆泥
This is neat. Steak, mashed potatoes,
小豌豆
little peas.
只是我最喜欢的每一个人
Just about every single one of my favorites.
我应该采取哑剧 休斯先生？
Should I take mime, Mr. Hughes?
他们说这是视觉才是最重要
They say it's the visual that counts.
一张照片的胜过千言万语
A picture's worth a thousand words.
和明星全在你怎么处理你的身体
And stardom's all in how you carry your body.
这是真的拉娜特纳了哑剧？
Is it true Lana Turner took mime?
我想我刚才的所有困惑
I guess I'm just all confused.
什么材料我会做
What material will I do
当你做我的斯特拉星光屏幕测试？
when you do my screen test for Stella Starlight?
尼斯
Nice.
是
Yes.
这就是人造丝 你知道
That's rayon, you know,
美国粘胶公司
the American Viscose Corporation
开战前进行人造丝
started making rayon before the war.
好东西
Good stuff.
- 你好？ - 是的？
- Hello? - Yes?
你看 我要你告诉阿诺德
Look, I want you to tell Arnold
该襟翼并不35.4
that the wing flaps are not 35.4.
他们是36.9
They're 36.9.
我告诉他 不是一次 而是两次！
I have told him that not once, but twice!
所以照顾它！
So take care of it!
Hughes先生
Mr. Hughes,
我不知道如果我有天赋
I don't know if I have the talent
成功的电影
to be successful in the movies,
但我觉得我做的
but I think I do.
而且我不是你的失败侮辱我见面越快
And I'm not insulted by your failure to meet me sooner
因为我知道你有自己的做事方式
because I know you have your own way of doing things.
而且我可能是从弗吉尼亚州的一个土包子
And I may be a bumpkin from Virginia,
但我是一个虔诚的基督徒
but I'm a good Christian.
而我足够聪明 知道
And I'm smart enough to know
如果我听说过你的传闻
that if the rumors I've heard about you
妇女是真实的 你不会有时间
with women were true, you wouldn't have had time
开飞机 更别说创造一种
to fly a plane, let alone invent one
是否襟翼是35.4或36.9
whether the wing flaps were 35.4 or 36.9.
所以 我只希望我能赢得你尊重我的工作
So I only hope I can earn your respect for my work
因为你肯定能够赢得了我的尊重你
because you've certainly earned my respect for yours.
什么事这么好笑？
What is so funny?
嘿 我要忙着在屏幕测试
Hey, I'm gonna get busy on the screen test.
纳丁
Nadine.
有福救世主！
Blessed Savior!
你会打招呼纳丁给我吗？
Will you say hello to Nadine for me?
她是个宝
She's a treasure.
纳丁 我要忙碌起来的时候了
Nadine, I wanna get busy right away
在斯特拉星光屏幕测试
on the Stella Starlight screen test
对于玛拉马布里 好吗？
for Marla Mabrey, okay?
好 此外 确保
Good. Also, make sure
哈维修饰我的照片在我的毛衣
Harvey retouched the picture of me in my sweater.
好的
Okay.
谢谢 玛拉
Thanks, Marla.
谢谢！
Thank you!
那么是什么 他真正喜欢的？
So what's he really like?
我妈妈不能一直错误的
My mom could not have been more wrong.
共有绅士！ 惊人！
A total gentleman! Amazing!
我的意思是 是的 他也不年轻了
I mean, yes, he's not young.
但是这个人是一个令人难以置信的浪漫身影
But the man's an incredibly romantic figure.
我的意思是 让我们面对它 他的老
I mean, let's face it, he's old
但是大家对他有好感呢
but everybody's got a crush on him anyway.
我不知道这是否是钱
I don't know if it's the money
或电源 或神秘 或什么
or the power or the mystery or what.
这是愚蠢的
This is silly.
我是什么
What am I,
玛米•艾森豪威尔豪华轿车？
Mamie Eisenhower in a limousine?
我想 也许它会发生 现在 弗兰克
I think maybe it's gonna happen now, Frank.
我刚认识霍华德•休斯
I just met Howard Hughes.
弗兰克 这是凌晨3:15你看我吗？
Frank, that's 3:15 a.m. Do you read me?
罗杰凌晨3:15
Roger. 3:15 a.m.
什么是凌晨3:15？
What's 3:15 a.m.?
我和他见面
I'm meeting him.
我去接他这里 凌晨3:15
I pick him up here, 3:15 a.m.
这是一个大日子！
It is a big day!
我妈妈已经不能更错了！
My mom could not have been more wrong!
这是水
That's water.
从缅因州
From Maine.
水
Water.
从缅因州
From Maine.
你长大的房子没多少浴室有哪些？
How many bathrooms did the house you grew up in have?
一
One.
我也是
Mine, too.
保持梦想的房子
Keep dreaming about that house.
我一直在敲墙出
I keep knocking walls out
并使其越做越大
and making it bigger and bigger.
不不不 我需要知道 如果那个混蛋莱瓦尔
No, no, no. I need to know if that son of a bitch Levar,
与这些女孩的行为适当
is behaving appropriately with these girls.
顺便说一下
And by the way,
我不知道威尔伯无论是
I'm not sure about Wilbur either.
所以 今晚 我检查了这小子弗兰克•福布斯
So tonight, I'm checking out this kid Frank Forbes.
你有没有想过你会中呆坐着'
Did you ever think you'd be sittin' in
前院听洛杉矶爱乐乐团？
your front yard listening to the Los Angeles Philharmonic?
我们只是希望任何人看到我开车 你在前排座位
Let's just hope nobody saw me driving you in the front seat.
老实说 我真的很想让你知道
Frank, I really wanna let you know
当你告诉我的规则并不适用于我
that when you told me the rules don't apply to me
这是非常有帮助的
it was really helpful.
好
Good.
你知道 他们也不适用于您
You know, they don't apply to you either.
对
Right.
我想我们最好说晚安
I guess we better say good night.
是
Yes.
晚安
Good night.
嘿! 你在3:15有个约会
Hey! You've got a date at 3:15.
鲍比达林不是由后来来了吗？
Bobby Darin's not coming by later?
休斯先生 我是弗兰克
Mr. Hughes, I'm Frank.
这真是一种荣幸
It's really an honor
有机会开车送你 休斯先生
to have the opportunity to drive you, Mr. Hughes.
我没有......我没有......
I didn't... I wasn't...
我不知道我会...
I didn't know I'd be...
它会发生 我会驾驶你 但我...
It would happen that I'd be driving you, but I...
......或者说 我会很...
...or that I'd be...
...见到你 我的意思
...meeting you, I mean.
这是一个不错的夜晚
It's a nice night.
嘿 你觉得莱瓦尔
Hey, do you think Levar
和威尔伯是那种家伙
and Wilbur are the kind of guys
谁可能对他们的妻子想花栗鼠？
who might wanna chippy on their wives?
- 活跃的 先生？ - 作弊
- Chippy, sir? - Cheat.
哦! 我觉得他们都是诚实的人 先生
Oh! I think they're both honest men, sir.
- 不老和疲惫 你知道吗？ - 不
- Not old and jaded, you know? - No.
是啊 因为这是一件事 我根本无法忍受
Yeah, because that's one thing I simply cannot abide
是一个已婚男人谁在他的妻子chippies
is a married man who chippies on his wife.
我要解雇他 你知道吗？
I have to fire him, you know?
如果有人为我工作
And if anybody working for me
想搭讪的关系
wants to strike up a relationship
与我们的合约演员之一
with one of our contract actresses
- 我要解雇他- 对
- I have to fire him. - Right.
- 我只是做... - 是啊
- I just have to do that... - Yeah.
他们告诉我 你是订婚到您的...
They told me you're engaged to be married to your...
- ...七年级的心上人？ - 是的
- ...seventh grade sweetheart? - Yes.
- 好了吗？ 是啊 - 是的 谢谢
- Is that good? Yeah. - Yes, thank you.
我很佩服
I admire that.
告诉我的东西
Tell me something.
是...什么是你对萨利的想法？
Is... What is your thinking on Sally?
或者 呃...或玛米 例如？
Or, uh... Or Mamie, for instance?
你觉得他们是直箭？
Do you think they're straight arrows?
- 直箭？ - 是啊
- Straight arrows? - Yeah.
或者苹果花女王难道她玩？
Or the Apple Blossom Queen. Does she play around?
玛拉马布里 你是什么意思？
Marla Mabrey, you mean?
玛拉马布里 是的她是快？
Marla Mabrey, yeah. Is she fast?
- 快？ - 快速淫乱是啊
- Fast? - Fast. Promiscuous. Yeah.
呵呵 好了 大家谁知道她说:
Oh, well, everybody who knows her says
她是他们见过的最虔诚的基督徒
she's the most devout Christian they've ever met.
真？ 而且她不喝酒？
Really? And does she drink?
我听说她从来没有在她的生活饮品 先生
I'm told she's never had a drink in her life, sir.
- 真的吗？ - 是的
- Really? - Yes.
- 她去教堂？ - 不远处的我自己
- She go to church? - Not far from my own.
您...
You...
你去教堂每个星期天？
You go to church every Sunday?
- 是的先生由于我是13 - 真的吗？
- Yes, Sir. Since I was 13. - Really?
要知道 这些女孩子都希望自己的车
You know, all these girls want their own cars.
但是我告诉你 如果你不赶他们
But I'm telling you, if you don't drive them,
你不能让他们的眼睛
you can't keep an eye on them.
而且它只是一个 它只是一个...
And it's just a, it's just a...
你得有
You gotta have
- 他们的门钥匙 - 是的
- their gate keys. - Yes.
他们的门的钥匙 因为我要告诉你......
The keys to their gate, because I'm telling you...
性病在洛杉矶县的
Venereal disease in Los Angeles County's
- 一些东西像85％ - 真的吗？
- up something like 85%. - Really?
你熟悉可用的土地关闭穆赫兰道 先生？
Are you familiar with available land off Mulholland Drive, sir?
我们非常由塞尔在名为科尔顿的人留下深刻印象
We're very impressed by a guy named Colton at Searle.
而他似乎已经拿出东西的女士
And he seems to have come up with something for the ladies
所谓的避孕药
called a birth control pill.
- 计划生育？- 避孕药
- Birth control? - Birth control pill.
这是一个避孕这是Enovid
It's a contraceptive. It's Enovid.
如果你很聪明 你会买自己一些塞尔股票
If you're smart, you'll buy yourself some Searle stock.
嗯 谢谢你的小费 先生
Mmm. Thank you for that tip, sir.
你知道 罗氏公司
You know, Hoffmann-La Roche
刚刚通过FDA的新药
just got a new drug through the FDA.
这是一种抗抑郁药他们称这是利眠宁
It's an antidepressant. They're calling it Librium.
该公司的瑞士
The company's Swiss,
但他们有一个美国分部
but they've got an American division
由鲍勃•克拉克的名字CEO他是爱尔兰人的一部分
with a CEO by the name of Bob Clark. He's part Irish.
所以史克代替
So instead of Smith Kline,
或Merck 或普强 或辉瑞 甚至塞尔
or Merck, or Upjohn, or Pfizer, or even Searle,
你可能会想看一看罗氏公司
you might wanna take a look at Hoffmann-La Roche.
可能是一个存量的挫折感
Might be a heck of a stock.
嗯
Uh-huh.
A-哈！
A-ha!
哦 那很好
Oh, that's nice.
是啊
Yeah.
嗯
Hmm.
“对于食品和爱你的一切礼物
"For food and all Thy gifts of love,
“我们给你的感谢和赞扬
"we give Thee thanks and praise.
“往下看 哦耶稣 从上述
"Look down, Oh Jesus, from up above
“并祝福我们所有我们的日子阿门”
"and bless us all our days. Amen."
好了 现在 你是怎么想
Okay, now, what did you wanna
- 哦！ - 我推销穆赫兰道？
- Oh! - sell me on Mulholland Drive?
在我看来 先生
It looks to me, sir,
这可能是 对不起
that this might be, excuse me,
正确的时间买的土地非常独特的作品
the right time to buy a very unique piece of land.
它拥有117英亩它有一切
It's 117 acres. It's got everything.
它位于正上方穆赫兰...
It's located right above Mulholland...
你喜欢飞？
Do you like to fly?
- 飞？- 飞
- Fly? - Fly.
呃 不 先生
Um, no, sir.
- 没有？ - 不
- No? - No.
为什么？
Why?
嗯 我从来没有
Uh, I never have.
你永远不会有什么呢？
You never have what?
飞行在一个平面上
Flown in a plane.
你从来没有在飞机飞行？
You've never flown in a plane?
没有
No.
哦
Oh.
不 不 不 先生
No, no, no, sir.
先生 这一个是弗兰克•福布斯
Sir, this one's on Frank Forbes.
谁是弗兰克福布斯？
Who's Frank Forbes?
我接到你了！ 我给你的那一个！
I got you! I got you on that one!
你跟那一个 先生让我 是
You got me with that one, sir. Yes.
不 我知道你 弗兰克
No, I know you, Frank.
我知道你的一切你懂的？
I know all about you. You know that?
- 我知道你的一切 - 真的吗？
- I know all about you. - Really?
- 这东西 你知道... - MM-HMM
- This thing, you know... - Mm-hmm.
约两个半月 也许三个月
About two and a half months, maybe three months
要准备好进行测试
gonna be ready to test.
但是明天我们正在测试一个小飞机
But tomorrow we're testing a little plane.
真的吗？
Oh, really?
我想你和我在一起
And I want you there with me.
- 好的？- 是的先生
- Okay? - Yes, sir.
- 你明白？- 是的先生
- You understand? - Yes, sir.
- 你懂了？- 是的先生
- You get it? - Yes, sir.
好的 好
Okay. Good.
你知道 有时候我只是想在这里问世
You know, sometimes I just like to come out here
和刚坐下 有一个汉堡 只是谈谈我的飞机
and just sit, have a burger, and just talk to my plane.
嗨 飞机
Hi, plane.
问好我的飞机 你愿意吗？
Say hello to my plane, will you?
嗨 飞机
Hi, plane.
飞机 这是弗兰克
Plane, this is Frank.
明天 我们得到了小飞机
And tomorrow, we got the little plane.
休斯先生 你继续这个航班
Mr. Hughes, you continue this flight
在危害已支付了飞机的风险
at the risk of endangering a plane that has been paid for
由美国政府
by the government of the United States.
我试图降落该死的东西！
I am trying to land the goddamn thing!
休斯先生 得到你的安全频率
Mr. Hughes, get on your safety frequency.
请进来吧
Come in, please.
没有安全的频率
No safety frequency.
我是...
Do I...
一个小小的惊喜 是吧？
A little surprise, huh?
有用 是啊
It works. Yeah.
我觉得这一点 你喜欢它吗？
I feel this. Do you like it?
是的先生
Yes, sir.
请勿触摸可待因
Don't touch that codeine.
- 如果你能得到推... - 不要告诉我推什么！
- If you can get pushing... - Don't tell me what to push!
我发明了该死的东西！
I invented the goddamn thing!
及时为您灌肠 先生
Time for your enema, sir.
给该死的灌肠袋福布斯先生 请
Give the goddamn enema bag to Mr. Forbes, please.
是
Yes.
福布斯先生灌肠袋
Mr. Forbes. The enema bag.
你是我现在的事情 弗兰克信任的唯一的人
You're the only person I trust with that thing now, Frank.
我告诉你 这个涂料阻止你
I tell you, this dope stops you up.
它停止你
It stops you up.
你买一些节育股票
Buying you some of that birth control stock.
这会通过该死的屋顶
It's gonna go through the goddamn roof.
弗兰克 你知道我多大了
Frank, you know how old I was
当我从我的爸爸继承了休斯工具公司？
when I inherited the Hughes Tool Company from my daddy?
比你年轻
Younger than you.
休斯先生 我不知道
Mr. Hughes, I don't know
那我真的有资格...
that I'm really qualified to...
哦 那会是一个坏的疤痕
Oh, that's gonna be a bad scar.
我该怎么...
What do I...
我该怎么跟那怎么办？
What do I do with that?
我会检查它 福布斯先生
I'll check on it, Mr. Forbes.
拉娜特纳的玫瑰是比我的好
Lana Turner's roses are better than mine.
但看看这些！
But look at these!
雏菊
Daisies.
所以意想不到
So unexpected.
让彼得斯是聪明的
Jean Peters is smart.
福布斯先生 纳丁是在手机上
Mr. Forbes, Nadine is on the phone.
我从哪里来 雏菊很便宜
Where I come from, daisies are cheap.
- 是啊？ - 弗兰克 这是关于......
- Yeah? - Frank, it's about...
是的 你好 纳丁
Yes, hello, Nadine.
我一直在值班医院
I've been on duty at the hospital
百分百的我的时间
a hundred percent of my time.
这是一个小我很难算
It's a little difficult for me to count
有多少我用气加仑
how many gallons of gas that I used
休斯先生收到了他的意外
before Mr. Hughes had his accident.
谢谢
Thank you.
你已经上移
You've moved up.
福布斯先生
Mr. Forbes.
有一阵子了
It's been a while.
他们需要你
They need you.
好的 呃...
Okay. Uh...
鲍比达林不是送你的雏菊？
Bobby Darin's not sending you daisies?
好的 我知道了
Okay, fine. I get it.
我静坐在后座
I have to still sit in the back seat.
但是 如果我们打算吃午饭
But if we're going to lunch,
难道我们吃的同桌 还是......
do we eat at the same table, or...
不 我吃在厨房 当然
No. I'm eating in the kitchen, of course.
我想 你知道吗？
I think, you know what?
为什么你不开车吗？我应该坐在后座
Why don't you just drive? I should sit in the back seat.
我不知道我为什么 你知道...
I don't know why I'm, you know...
我想没有人可以说我们不遵守规则
I guess nobody can say we don't follow the rules.
“对于食品和爱你的一切礼物
"For food and all Thy gifts of love,
“我们给你的感谢和赞扬
"we give Thee thanks and praise.
“往下看 哦耶稣
"Look down, Oh Jesus,
“从上面和祝福我们所有我们的日子阿门”
"from above and bless us all our days. Amen."
阿门 我简直不敢相信
Amen. I can't believe it.
他终于走出了医院
He's finally out of the hospital,
并马上你飞往华盛顿？
and right away you fly to Washington?
你会想念我的屏幕测试
You're gonna miss my screen test.
我听说艾森豪威尔给他发了一封电报
I heard Eisenhower sent him a telegram.
如果艾森豪威尔真聪明
If Eisenhower was really smart,
他必须霍华德•休斯刚刚轰炸莫斯科
he'd have Howard Hughes just bomb Moscow,
并有共产主义圆满结束
and have communism over and done with.
我认为霍华德•休斯应该成为总统
I think Howard Hughes should be president.
有像他这样的人他是在另一个层面上
There's nobody like him. He's on another level.
严重的是 可怜的人
Seriously, the poor man,
他得处理这些TWA股东
he's gotta deal with these TWA stockholders
谁是捕蟹有关从螺旋桨移到飞机
who are crabbing about moving from propellers to jets.
与此同时
At the same time,
他现在已经说服美国参议院
he now has to convince the United States Senate
该大力士能飞
that the Hercules can fly.
所以 你会飞往华盛顿？
So you're gonna fly to Washington?
我不会飞谢谢你的慰问我将采取
I will not be flying. Thank you for asking. I will be taking
列车在清晨
the train early in the morning.
什么时候莎拉搬到洛杉矶？
When does Sarah move to LA?
嗯 好吧 我...
Um, well, I...
不知道萨拉和我是...
Don't know if Sarah and I are...
她还认为 一旦你已经亲密
She still believes that once you've been intimate
或走一路一个人
or gone all the way with a person,
在神的眼中
that in the eyes of God
你承诺的那个人
you're committed to that person
你的余生
for the rest of your life.
所以她认为 因为你和她有...
So she believes since you and she have...
...走了一路 说你已经结婚了吗？
...gone all the way, that you're already married?
我同意萨拉
I agree with Sarah.
这就是为什么我从来没有做过
That's why I've never done it.
这就是为什么我在等待 因为我已经是肯定的
That's why I'm waiting, because I have to be sure.
那么这 我的意思是 这是一个小...
Well that's, I mean, that's a little...
我没有合法结婚
I'm not legally married.
参议员 我来到这里作证
Senator, I have come here to testify
我自己的自由意志
of my own free will.
参议员 我来到这里作证我自己的自由意志
Senator, I have come here to testify of my own free will.
等待 参议员
Wait. Senator,
我来到这里作证我自己的自由意志
I have come here to testify of my own free will.
参议员 我来到这里作证我自己的自由意志
Senator, I have come here to testify of my own free will.
对我的任何可能性字...
Any word on the possibility of me...
......得到一个股票磁带游行？
...getting a ticker tape parade?
他们没有股票磁带游行在华盛顿 霍华德
They don't have ticker tape parades in Washington, Howard.
这里没有摩天大楼
There are no skyscrapers here.
你以为我不知道你打算怎么办？
Do you think I don't know what you're planning?
我正打算？
What I'm planning?
什么你打算你以为我是坚果 对不对？
What you're planning. You think I'm nuts, right?
你以为我疯了
You think I'm nuts.
霍华德 我只说了
Howard, all I said was,
我想你应该看到有人
I think you should see someone.
“看到有人？”
"See someone?"
我真的觉得你需要帮助 孩子
I really think you need help, kid.
看到别人？
See someone?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
你知道 我试图移动
Do you realize that I'm trying to move
从螺旋桨飞机到整个航空公司？
an entire airline from propellers to jets?
而股东可以听到
And the stockholders could hear
我坐在疯人院
that I am sitting in a loony bin
锁定了一些心理医生
locked up with some psychiatrist
谁可以宣布我是不称职
who can declare me to be incompetent
然后我得给整个该死的业务
and then I have to give the whole goddamn business
在一些该死的储油？
over to some goddamn conservator?
你知不知道？
You do realize that?
我会在我的房间里 霍华德
I'll be in my room, Howard.
你在看什么？
What are you looking at?
你有什么想法？说出来
You got any ideas? Speak up.
我认为你代表了广大本委员会
I think you represent to the majority of this committee,
什么是伟大的资本主义 而不是共产主义
what is great about capitalism as opposed to communism.
我觉得这些人都是怕你
I think these people are scared of you,
我认为他们想成为你
and I think they wanna be you.
我不认为你要练
I don't think you have to practice
你会得到什么这样说
what you're gonna say like this.
我觉得你可以去那里
I think you can go in there,
并尝试甚至不知道
and try not even knowing
你会说什么 直到你说出来
what you're gonna say until you say it.
而你没有 在我看来 会讲错话
And you're not, in my opinion, gonna say the wrong thing.
嗯
Huh.
你懂...
You know...
你知道我多大了 当我接过我爸爸的公司？
You know how old I was when I took over my daddy's company?
我比你年轻
I was younger than you.
我告诉你的？
Did I tell you that?
胶卷
Roll film.
好的 亲爱的 放松
Okay. Darling, relax.
告诉我们一些关于你自己
Tell us a little about yourself.
好的 我从福隆罗雅 弗吉尼亚州来的
Okay. I'm from Front Royal, Virginia.
我一直感兴趣的言论和戏剧
I've always been interested in speech and dramatics.
- 我写的歌 - 转到您的左边
- I write songs. - Turn to your left.
你可以提高你的下巴了一点？
Can you raise your chin up a little?
大 一直在说话
Great. Keep talking.
我本来打算去玛丽•华盛顿大学
I was going to go to Mary Washington College,
在这里我打算主修英语
where I intended to major in English.
好了 你可以把你的吗？
Okay, can you turn to your right?
但是要说话 下巴英语专业 继续下去
But keep talking, and chin up. Major in English, go on.
嗯...
Um...
但我决定当我赢得了才艺比赛
But I decided when I won a talent contest
也许我给它在好莱坞一展身手
that maybe I'd give it a go in Hollywood.
好了 你可以把你的吗？
Okay, can you turn to your right?
伟大的 伟大的 伟大 好的
Great, great, great. Okay.
你唱歌吗？
Do you sing?
好吧 排序
Well, sort of.
我要保持说话？
Should I keep talking?
好了 谈谈你的左边
Okay, turn to your left.
你游泳吗？
Do you swim?
当然！
Sure!
衣柜 我们有什么泳衣？
Wardrobe, do we have any bathing suits?
如果你曾经想溜出去吃点什么的
If you ever wanted to slip out for a bite or something,
我想我们可以做到这一点的雷达之下
I think we could do that under the radar.
Hughes先生
Mr. Hughes,
美国人想知道 如果有人
the American people wanna know if someone
正在对不能开飞机利润！
is making a profit on a plane that can't fly!
参议员...
Senator...
我来到这里作证我自己的自由意志
I have come here to testify of my own free will.
没有人做任何的利润
Nobody's making any profit.
此平面将用于测试和研究
This plane will be used for testing and research
和推进航空领域在这个国家
and advancing the art of aviation in this country.
再过几天 它会飞翔
In a few more days, it'll fly.
我已经指出 如果它是失败的
I have stated that if it were to be a failure,
我将离开这个国家 永远不再回来
I would leave this country and never come back.
我的意思吧！
And I mean it!
它会飞翔 参议员
It'll fly, Senator.
它会飞翔
It'll fly.
霍华德•休斯的巨型飞机已经飞行
Howard Hughes's giant plane has flown.
而在控制中 成功的设计师 建设者 所有者
And at the controls, the successful designer, builder, owner,
空速纪录保持者 千万富翁本人
airspeed record holder, multimillionaire himself,
霍华德•休斯
Howard Hughes.
Bravo！
Bravo!
亿万富翁 该死的它 而不是百万富翁
Billionaire, goddamn it, not millionaire.
而什么是地狱发生在我身上的特写
And what the hell happened to the close-up of me
在驾驶舱？你懂
in the cockpit? You know,
飞机飞了一里路
the plane flew for one mile,
没有人知道它是否还能再飞
and nobody knows if it'll ever fly again.
他们知道什么是它的成本那请问我没有好
And they know what it cost. That does me no good
在TWA好吧 谢谢你 先生
at TWA. All right, thank you, gentlemen.
非常感谢你 格雷格？
Thank you very much. Greg?
是的 霍华德？
Yes, Howard?
霍华德？
Howard?
我得知道我得采取什么法律措施
I gotta know what legal steps I gotta take
让这些人从心理医生坚持我
to keep these people from sticking me with a psychiatrist,
然后犯我精神病院......
and then committing me to an insane asylum...
然后宣布我是不称职
Then declaring me to be incompetent,
然后翻我的整个业务到了储油
and then turning over my entire business to a conservator.
你得告诉我 我有什么做的？
You gotta tell me what I have to do...
依法阻止他们这样做 好吗？
To legally keep them from doing that, okay?
给我回电话
Call me back.
你好？
Hello?
你好 小姐
Hello, ma'am.
笔者获悉
I was informed that
你的电视天线是有缺陷的
your television antenna was defective.
我带来了最新款
I brought over the newest model.
而我 如果你会知道...
And I was wondering if you would...
我刚才看到你的屏幕测试你很棒
I just saw your screen test. You were great.
这是伟大的！
It was great!
真？
Really?
嗯...我认为这是非常可怕的！
Well... I thought it was pretty awful!
你很棒
You were great.
他们只是想看看我在游泳衣！
They just wanted to see me in a bathing suit!
我没有这样做
I didn't do it.
但他们并没有说什么时候结束
But they didn't say anything when it was over.
你已经得到的东西这些家伙
You've got something these guys
甚至不知道呢
don't even know about yet.
我的意思是 等到霍华德•休斯看到它
I mean, wait till Howard Hughes sees it.
我有两个以上的这些在车上 以防万一
I have two more of these in the car, just in case.
雏菊
Daisies.
而不是从吉恩彼得斯？
And not from Jean Peters?
那么 他们可能是他们可以从任何人
Well, they could be. They could be from anybody.
他们只是按照规则 不能从我这里
They just, according to the rules, can't be from me.
我工作的一部分我工作的一部分
Part of my job. Part of my job.
♪有一天 我告诉我的朋友♪
♪ One day I told my friend ♪
♪我是可怕的蓝色♪
♪ I was terribly blue ♪
♪是不是为时已晚做♪
♪ Was it far too late to do ♪
♪我梦见我会做什么？♪
♪ What I dreamed I would do? ♪
♪他想了一会儿 然后他回答♪
♪ He thought for a moment, then he answered ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用于你♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply to you ♪
♪他说 很简单地 静静地过♪
♪ He said it very simply and quietly too ♪
♪不过好像有没有任何疑问 都♪
♪ But as if there wasn't any doubt at all ♪
♪ 他知道♪
♪ That he knew ♪
♪他给我的礼物♪
♪ He gave me a gift ♪
♪我会珍惜♪
♪ That I would treasure ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply ♪
♪要你♪
♪ To you ♪
♪在我们看到的电影♪
♪ In the movies we see ♪
♪在电视上的节目♪
♪ In the shows on TV ♪
♪而在国歌热情演唱♪
♪ And in anthems passionately sung ♪
♪有 你有一个消息♪
♪ There's a message that you've got ♪
♪为了让自己相信♪
♪ To keep believing in yourself ♪
♪但他们通常是指如果你还年轻♪
♪ But they generally mean if you're young ♪
♪是它写在空中 因为它似乎是♪
♪ Is it written in the air As it seems to be ♪
♪我们还没有长在所有要找到我们的命运♪
♪ That we haven't long at all To find our destiny ♪
♪我会永远记得感恩♪
♪ I'll always remember to be grateful ♪
♪这个规则不适用♪
♪ That the rules don't apply ♪
♪对我来说♪
♪ To me ♪
那是谁？
Who is that?
这是莱瓦尔
It's Levar.
- 什么？ - 他让我上课
- What? - He's driving me to class.
这是我的错
This is my fault.
这是我的错 这是我的错
This is all my fault. This is my fault.
不 不这不是你的错
No, no. This is not your fault.
这是我的错 这是我的错
This is all my fault. This is my fault.
而且它的罚款让我们面对它 它的罚款
And it's fine. Let's face it, it's fine.
我唱你的歌曲
I sang you the song.
这是我的错
This is my fault.
This is all my fault.
有一个扫帚和簸箕在那里 好吗？
There's a broom and a dustpan in there, okay?
等待 告诉我莱瓦尔带来的天线 好的
Wait, tell Levar I brought the antenna. Okay.
嗨 进来吧
Hi, come on in.
嗨
Hi.
哦 我和弗兰克试图以腾出空间
Oh, Frank and I were trying to make space
- 电视机和... - 哇
- for the TV and... - Wow.
- 让我来帮你 - 谢谢！
- Let me help you with that. - Thanks!
当然
Sure.
等待什么 现在是什么时候？我们要去上课迟到
Wait. What, what time is it? We're gonna be late for class.
哦 不 你不能去上课
Oh, no, you're not going to class.
休斯先生要见你
Mr. Hughes wants to see you.
现在？
Now?
是啊 是啊 我还以为他们叫你
Yeah, yeah, I thought they called you.
我应该把你在那边
I'm supposed to take you over there.
嘿 莱瓦尔
Hey, Levar.
嗨 弗兰克
Hi, Frank.
他们把我送到了新天线
They sent me over with the new antenna.
它没有工作 虽然
It didn't work though.
我们试图移动电视
We were trying to move the TV.
- 我会去做 我会做的 - 不不不
- I'll do that. I'll do it. - No, no, no.
我会的 我会的是啊 小心你的脚
I'll do that, I'll do that. Yeah, be careful of your feet.
我会从车上其他天线
I'll get the other antennas from the car.
没有！我会去做！因为我知道 你迟到了所以 我会得到他们
No! I'll do that! Because I know that you're late. So I'll get them.
男孩
Boy.
我 呃...
I'm, uh...
我会得到一些毛巾
I'm gonna get some towels.
我只是不知道如何站和教堂
I just don't know how this stands with the church.
对不起 我会去弗雷斯诺
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go to Fresno.
- 我会讲莎拉- 你结婚了！
- I'm gonna talk to Sarah. - You're married!
你是一个已婚男人！
You're a married man!
- 我会说实话她- 我知道！
- I'm gonna be honest with her. - I know that!
- 因为我已经与她...... - 你说得对
- I have been with her since... - You're right.
......我们在七年级在一起
...we were in the seventh grade together.
什么发生了我们是不是你的错
What's been happening with us is not your fault.
但我的表现就像一个廉价floozy
But I've behaved like a cheap floozy.
你听不到我在说什么
You're not hearing what I'm saying.
我不是处女的一些恶心的挑逗......
I'm not some disgusting tease of a virgin...
- 你没有做错任何事！ - ......想偷
- You've done nothing wrong! - ...trying to steal
另一个女人的丈夫你在听我说吗？
another woman's husband. Are you listening to me?
你不听我在说什么
You're not listening to what I'm saying.
我不是试图窃取另一个女人的丈夫
I am not trying to steal another woman's husband.
- 你没有做错任何事 - 你不是奸夫
- You've done nothing wrong. - You're not an adulterer.
你已经结婚了 弗兰克
You're married, Frank.
- 你不是... - 你...
- You're not... - You're...
需要帮忙？
Need help?
不 谢谢 莱瓦尔我只是想改变我的衣服谢谢 弗兰克
No, thanks, Levar. I'm just gonna change my clothes. Thanks, Frank.
回头见
See you later.
我雇你为我双 因为你看起来就像我的
I hired you as my double because you look exactly like me.
鞋子都是错误的现在 离开这里
The shoes are all wrong. Now, get out of here.
他们将更加严格接下来的时间 先生
They'll be more exacting next time, sir.
好的 那 那你不能合法
Okay. That, that you cannot legally
承诺人送进了疯人院
commit a person to an insane asylum
如果他们结婚 他们的配偶拒绝承诺呢？
if they are married and their spouse refuses to commit to it?
- 是的先生- 嗯
- Yes, sir. - Uh-huh.
哦 如果有什么没有配偶？
Well, what if there is no spouse?
格雷格 我得到了3万多人为我工作
Greg, I got 30,000 people working for me
在武器上 五角大楼会相信没人做
on weapons the Pentagon would trust nobody else to do,
而你告诉我出去
and you're telling me go out
并得到妻子留出了疯人院的？
and get a wife to stay out of the loony bin?
您的会议结束后 你会想
After your meeting, what would you think about
溜出一些地方完全私人的？
sneaking out some place totally private?
是的 环布赖恩•福雷斯特 请
Yes, ring Mr. Brian Forester, please.
布赖恩森林人
Brian Forester.
这是霍华德•休斯
This is Howard Hughes.
您好 Hughes先生
Hello, Mr. Hughes.
我们已经走过了漫长的道路 先生 讨论TWA我们只是希望
We've traveled a long way, sir, to discuss TWA. We were just hoping
我们可以跳过 并说很快招呼
we could skip over and say a quick hello.
我们是在同一个旅馆 毕竟
We're in the same hotel, after all.
你可能只是几英尺远！
You could just be a few feet away!
我非常抱歉 福雷斯特
I'm terribly sorry, Mr. Forester.
一会儿再和你说
I will talk to you later.
嗨 想要一些冰淇淋吗？
Hi. Want some ice cream?
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
在最高位 是的是的 那很好
Bit on top. Yes, yes. That's good.
- 这位年轻的女士就在这里 休斯先生 - 哦
- The young lady is here, Mr. Hughes. - Oh.
此外 福雷斯特 美林的人
Also, Mr. Forester, the Merrill Lynch man,
- 再次呼吁- 嗯
- called again. - Uh-huh.
他们在平房8-A
They're in bungalow 8-A.
他们想知道你是哪的平房
They wanna know which bungalow you're in.
嗯
Uh-huh.
他们想看看你
They wanna see you.
没有必要对任何人知道我在什么平房
There's no need for anyone to know what bungalow I'm in.
是啊 只要给我...是啊 是啊 是啊...
Yeah, just give me... Yeah, yeah, yeah...
好 好 好 好的 而且 你可以把...
Good, good, good. Okay. And, you can take...
小心
Be careful.
是啊 因为......
Yeah, because...
你 呃...
You, uh...
嗯
Uh-huh.
是啊 那很好
Yeah, yeah. That's good.
而多一点点了 那很好
And a little bit more over. That's good.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
Argh！ 把那人离开这里！
Argh! Get that person outta here!
让我们找到自己的妈妈和爸爸
Let's find your mommy and daddy.
那么 我们这个发型还是没有完成？
So are we finished with this haircut or not?
我怎么会知道？他非常严格
How should I know? He's very exacting.
严格甚至不是对这个词
Exacting's not even the word for that.
我不喜欢看他！
I don't look like him!
所以 现在你告诉我
So now you're telling me
只是去结婚某人
to just go get married to somebody
谁是不够好 留人
who's nice enough to keep people
从派我精神病院？
from putting me into an insane asylum?
另外 我运行失控可待因
Also, I'm running outta codeine.
莎拉 我们应该采取一点点时间
Sarah, we should take a little bit of time.
我们需要花时间去思考
We need to take time to think.
嗯 你好
Well, hello.
你说什么？
What did you say?
我说你好！
I said hello!
MM-HMM
Mm-hmm.
它已经有一段时间 休斯先生
It's been a while, Mr. Hughes.
嗯？
Huh?
自从我们遇见它已经有一段时间
It's been a while since we met.
我从福雷斯特电话留言
I have a telephone message from Mr. Forester.
阅读
Read it.
“我们来到您的要求借给你
"We came at your request to lend you
- “$ 400亿TWA - MM-HMM
- "$400 million for TWA. - Mm-hmm.
“难道我们不应该至少被允许见到你
"Shouldn't we at least be allowed to meet you,
“因为谁控制TWA的人
"as the person who controls TWA,
“面对面？”
"face-to-face?"
他叫什么音？
What was his tone?
- 紧张 - 服务？
- Nervous. - Service?
紧张！
Nervous!
啊 是的 好吧 好吧 谢谢你
Ah, yeah. Well, okay, thank you.
是啊 这已经
Yeah, it has been
因为我们可以看到彼此 玛拉一段时间
a while since we were able to see one another, Marla.
每个星期我看到我检查你的名字
I do see your name on my check every week.
这有点像见到你
That's sort of like seeing you.
你会原谅我吗？
Would you excuse me?
关闭门
Shut the door.
这到底是她在这里干什么？
What the hell is she doin' here?
你说你想用两个M的女孩
You said you wanted the girl with the two M's.
这不是她 这就是玛拉马布里
That's not her. That's Marla Mabrey.
她是一个浸信会的修女 为基督的缘故
She's a Baptist nun, for Christ's sake.
这是工资单上唯一一个拥有两个M的
That's the only one on the payroll with two M's.
它是否出现你 也许一
Did it occur to you that maybe the one
我想用两个M的不是工资单上？
that I wanted with the two M's was not on the payroll?
啊! 你的意思是玛丽莲梦露？
Ah! You meant Marilyn Monroe?
谁？
Who?
玛丽莲•梦露？她吗？
Marilyn Monroe? Her?
是! 玛丽莲•梦露！
Yes! Marilyn Monroe!
我会得到一次摆脱她我很抱歉 先生
I'll get rid of her at once. I apologize, sir.
- 玛丽莲我会得到玛丽莲 - 号嘿 等等 等等......
- Marilyn. I'll get Marilyn. - No. Hey, wait, wait...
我会干掉她你走在回家
I'll get rid of her. You go on home.
如何是你的妈妈呢？
How's your mother?
她很好
She's very well.
嗯
Uh-huh.
银行家
Bankers.
大男孩从纽约
Big boys from New York.
从我读
From what I read,
银行家们在极其常规的方式工作
bankers work in extremely conventional ways.
我不假装理解航空业
I don't pretend to understand the airline business,
但我告诉你说的螺旋桨
but I'm told you say propellers
是过去的事情了
are a thing of the past.
好吧 我想你妈妈大概以为我是没关系
Well, I think your mother probably thought I was okay
只要她敢肯定
as long as she was sure that
我们有什么也没做对方
we had nothin' to do with each other.
我想她想 如果我一直
I think she thought that if I had been
只是那些女孩之一
just one of those girls
你不会有我的诚信真正的尊重
you wouldn't have real respect for my integrity.
啊
Ah.
我的意思是 我想一个女孩总是
I mean, I guess a girl's always
有一个信誉思考的问题
got a reputation to think about.
嗯 我想一个人总是
Well, I guess a man always
有名誉思考的问题
has a reputation to think about.
- 呃... - 喂？
- Uh... - Hello?
福雷斯特？
Mr. Forester?
休斯先生？
Mr. Hughes?
听着 我不认为有任何真正的
Listen, I don't think there's any real
必要性 我们能够满足
necessity for us to meet.
我的意思是 没有理由我们不能做到这一点
I mean, there's no reason why we can't do this
在电话
on the telephone.
好吧 让我平淡的 先生
Well, let me be plain, sir.
我没有被授权核准其风险借给你
I am not authorized to approve our venture to lend you
$ 400万美元 除非我们见面
$400 million unless we meet.
休斯先生？
Mr. Hughes?
如果有一个斯特拉星光脚本
If there's a Stella Starlight script,
你可以愚弄了我
you could have fooled me.
你看看我的屏幕测试？
Did you look at my screen test?
休斯先生 请你只
Mr. Hughes, please just
告诉我们你现在的平房
tell us what bungalow you're in.
这将是如此很容易的
It would be so very easy.
我们是 我们在14英尺的距离五英尺远的地方？二十英尺远的地方？
We're, we're 14 feet away. Five feet away? Twenty feet away?
哪一个是你的平房？ 我们会来找你！
Which one is your bungalow? We'll come to you!
呃 福雷斯特...
Uh, Mr. Forester...
对不起 我不认为有任何
I'm sorry, I don't think there's any
需要我们真正见面
need for us to actually meet.
没有理由为什么我们不应该
There's no reason why we shouldn't
能够做到这一点的电话
be able to do this on the telephone.
休斯先生？
Mr. Hughes?
这些人希望有一个面对面的面对面会议和我在一起
These guys wanna have a face-to-face meeting with me,
然后就可以说我疯了
and then be able to say I'm crazy.
然后 我将不得不放弃控制权
And then I'll have to give up control
TWA的给他们只是...
of TWA to them. It's just...
好吧 也许你会教给他们一个教训
Well, maybe you'd teach them a lesson
如果你只是把它给了他们
if you just gave it to them.
然后 他们可以起诉我一大堆钱
Then they could sue me for a whole lot of money,
然后他们可以来我爸爸的公司后
and then they may come after my daddy's company,
所以我真的不能让他们
and so I really can't afford to let them
让我某种精神情况
make me some kind of a psychiatric case.
我将离开这个国家 永远不再回来
I would leave this country and never come back.
我要离开这个国家 永不回来
I'd leave this country, and never come back.
你懂？
You know?
我要离开这个国家 永不回来
I'd leave this country, and never come back.
我不会什么 做到这一点
What, I'm not gonna do it.
他们只是有一张脸对脸会见了我
They just have a face-to-face meeting with me,
然后打电话给我一个螺母？
and then call me a nut?
嗯 这是荒谬的！
Well, that's ridiculous!
你有你在身边所有的自己人
And you have all your own people around you
你知道谁是可以信任的
who you know you can trust.
我可以给你一些建议？
May I give you some advice?
是
Yes.
永远不要相信任何人
Never trust anybody.
不是我 不是任何人
Not me, not anybody.
他们不是你的妈妈或你的爸爸
They're not your mommy or your daddy.
你可以信任的唯一的人是你
The only person you can trust is you.
你有孩子吗？
Do you have children?
我？
Me?
- 没有？ - 不
- No? - No.
恐怕我还多了父亲的儿子
I'm afraid that I'm still more of a son than a father.
但是我要告诉你事端非常重要的
But I'll tell you somethin' very important,
一对夫妇limeys的想出了
that a couple of limeys came up with
三 四年前
three or four years ago.
所谓DNA的小东西
Little thing called DNA,
我们正在干活用它在我的基金会
and we're workin' with it over at my foundation.
从某种意义上说 你是你的父亲
In a sense, you are your father,
因为他的DNA仍然是你的内心
because his DNA is still inside of you.
它让布莱恩'
It keeps goin' on,
和你的父亲没有什么可说的
and your father had nothing to say about it.
这是什么使他仍然活着
That's what makes him still alive.
的DNA 脱氧核糖核酸
DNA, deoxyribonucleic acid.
它有所有的遗传指令
It's got all the genetic instructions
导致所有所有的功能和开发
that cause all of the function and development of all
已知的活生物体这是基本的
known living organisms. It's the basic,
遗传物质的人类
hereditary material in human beings,
它要去复制 并复制 和复制
and it's gonna replicate, and replicate, and replicate,
我们是否希望它与否
whether we want it to or not.
你没有选择它只是会继续下去
You have no choice. It's just gonna keep going.
这是要去让你活着
It's gonna keep you alive.
如果斯特拉星光唱？
What if Stella Starlight sang?
要知道 使影片的音乐
You know, make the movie a musical.
我能唱歌！
I can sing!
好了 但没有人应该有孩子
Well, but nobody should have children
如果他们不想要这是肯定的
if they don't want to. That's for sure.
是啊 算了 反正
Yeah. Well, anyway,
如果我我爸爸的公司亏损 它会像失去了我的爸爸
if I lost my daddy's company, it'd be like losing my daddy.
这些财务人员豺
Those finance people are jackals.
豺狼？
Jackals?
豺狼
Jackals.
你为什么要和他们见面？
Why should you meet with them?
还等什么 如果你重复自己很多吗？
And so what if you repeat yourself a lot?
它增加了强调
It adds emphasis.
重点？
Emphasis?
你有没有从我疯了的人听说过吗？
Have you heard from people that I'm crazy?
好吧 如果你是什么疯狂的话
Well, if what you are is crazy, then,
然后给我更疯狂！
then give me more crazy!
你不是疯了你只是...
You're not crazy. You're just...
聪明
Smart.
你是不是像其他人一样
You are not like other people.
你是个例外
You're an exception.
你好？
Hello?
- 休斯先生？ - 嗯...
- Mr. Hughes? - Um...
我不打算要能和你说话 直到后来
I am not going to be able to talk to you until later.
后来是什么？
What is later?
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
休斯先生？
Mr. Hughes?
想听一首小歌我写的？
Wanna hear a little song I wrote?
♪有一天 我告诉我的朋友♪
♪ One day I told my friend ♪
♪我是可怕的蓝色♪
♪ I was terribly blue ♪
♪是不是为时已晚做♪
♪ Was it far too late to do ♪
♪我的梦想 我会做♪
♪ What I dreamed I would do ♪
♪他想了一会儿 然后他回答♪
♪ He thought for a moment then he answered ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用于你♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply to you ♪
♪在我们看到的电影♪
♪ In the movies we see ♪
♪在电视上的节目♪
♪ In the shows on TV ♪
♪而在国歌热情演唱♪
♪ And in anthems passionately sung ♪
♪有 你有一个消息♪
♪ There's a message that you've got ♪
♪为了让自己相信♪
♪ To keep believing in yourself ♪
♪但他们通常是指如果你还年轻♪
♪ But they generally mean if you're young ♪
♪你说你的感觉破♪
♪ You say you're feeling broken ♪
♪这么可怕的蓝色♪
♪ So terribly blue ♪
♪ “因为它是为时已晚做♪
♪ 'Cause it's far too late to do ♪
♪你梦见你会做什么♪
♪ What you dreamed you would do ♪
♪但我会告诉你一个秘密♪
♪ But I'll tell you a secret ♪
♪我向上帝发誓 这是真的♪
♪ And I swear to God it's true ♪
你让一个老家伙勇敢 玛拉
You make an old guy courageous, Marla.
那是一种恭维 霍华德？
Is that a compliment, Howard?
你不给我打电话Hughes先生
You're not calling me Mr. Hughes.
让我觉得年轻多了
Makes me feel so much younger.
好 霍华德！
Good, Howard!
现在 你怎么想快要忘记
Now, how would you like to forget about
将整个美国航空业
bringing the entire American aerospace industry
进入未来的必然
into the inevitable future
和驱动器的棕榈泉在汽车？
and drive to Palm Springs in a car?
他们说 这就像天堂
They say it's like heaven.
如果我有车 我要驱车你
If I had a car, I'd drive you there.
所有你的女孩应该有车
All you girls should have cars.
我们应该撕毁您的期限劳动合同
And we should tear up your term contract
而只是让画面三年的一年
and just make it a picture a year for three years.
$ 100,000画 好不好？
$100,000 a picture, okay?
它似乎并不真实的我
It doesn't seem real to me.
这就是真实
That's what's real.
你认为这是疯狂的 相信自己的直觉？
You think it's crazy to trust your gut instinct?
“有在人的事务大潮中
"There is a tide in the affairs of men,
“这在洪水牵头采取发财
"which taken at the flood lead on to fortune.
“省略 所有他们人生的旅途
"Omitted, all the voyage of their life
“在浅滩和苦难的约束”
"is bound in shallows and in miseries."
是
Yes.
“有一切的时候
"There is a time for everything.
“一个收获时间和时间播种
"A time to reap and a time to sow.
“一时间 从拥抱弃权
"A time to abstain from embracing,
“还有就是拥抱的时候”
"and there is a time to embrace."
我们并不需要一个和平的正义
We don't need a justice of the peace.
有了这个戒指 我娶你
With this ring, I thee wed.
等待
Wait.
小心
Careful.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊 而已
Yeah. That's it.
你的意思是 我们需要时间去思考？
What do you mean we need time to think?
我只是 我的意思是...
I just, I mean that...
自从七年级 我们一直在思考
We've been thinking since the seventh grade.
我只能说 我们应该采取一点点时间
I only mean that we should take a little bit of time.
你知道 我们不是在七年级了
You know, we're not in the seventh grade anymore.
我只是说 它可能...
I'm just saying it's probably...
你的意思是你需要时间去思考
You mean you need time to think.
给我格雷格
Get me Greg.
是的 霍华德？
Yes, Howard?
- 格雷格？ - 是的？
- Greg? - Yes?
我已经改变了主意获取了飞机
I've changed my mind. Get the plane.
我要去拉斯维加斯一小时
I'm going to Vegas in one hour.
霍华德 没有空气...
Howard, no air...
休斯先生 你要不要我的钱？
Mr. Hughes, do you want my money?
你想我的钱？
Do you want my money?
你想要我的钱没有？
Do you want my money or not?
与TWA见鬼去吧 你王八蛋！
The hell with TWA, you son of a bitch!
我们飞美航回到纽约！
We're flying American Airlines back to New York!
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
哇！
Wow!
这很棒！
This is great!
他们给所有女孩的汽车
They're giving all the girls cars.
他们告诉我 在总部
They told me at headquarters.
但我不能让我的开始
But I can't make mine start.
- 真的吗？ - 不
- Really? - No.
难道你要我......
Do you want me to...
嗯...
Um...
- 它可能淹没 - 水淹？
- It's probably flooded. - Flooded?
是啊 它淹没
Yeah. It's flooded.
嗯 你必须等待一点点
Um, you have to wait a little.
难道有人给了你？
Did somebody give that to you?
谁给了你？
Who gave that to you?
你是个已婚男人 弗兰克
You're a married man, Frank.
- 我...... - 谁给了你？
- I... - Who gave that to you?
我不能跟你了这一点
I can't do this with you anymore.
我看到一个人
I'm seeing someone.
它是私人的
It's private.
我不会跟你讨论
I'm not gonna discuss it with you.
- 你好？ - 你好？
- Hello? - Hello?
- 纳丁！ - 是的？
- Nadine! - Yes?
嗨 这是玛拉
Hi, it's Marla.
玛拉 喜
Marla, hi.
请你问休斯先生给我回电话？
Would you please ask Mr. Hughes to call me back?
对不起 玛拉所有我能说的是
I'm sorry, Marla. All I can say is
他会是出城了一个月
he's gonna be out of town for a month.
可能5周
Possibly five weeks.
我可以帮助什么吗？
Anything I can help with?
嗯 你可以告诉他 我已经决定
Well, could you tell him I've decided
反对该协议 我们讨论？
against the agreement we discussed?
我不能做到 我不能做到这一点
I can't do it. I just can't do it.
我会给他留言
I'll give him your message.
好的 谢谢
Okay. Thank you.
我曾经有一个生命
I used to have a life.
沃尔特•奥马利
Walter O'Malley,
布鲁克林道奇队的老板
the owner of the Brooklyn Dodgers
已经宣布球队将搬到洛杉矶
has announced the team will be moving to Los Angeles.
此外 公告只是关于霍华德•休斯
Also, a bulletin just in about Howard Hughes.
霍华德•休斯刚刚宣布 他已结婚
Howard Hughes just announced he's married.
而你不知道 他娶了一位女演员
And wouldn't you know, he married an actress.
新的休斯夫人
The new Mrs. Hughes is
好莱坞女星 让彼得斯
Hollywood actress, Jean Peters.
其他消息方面 国务院总理赫鲁晓夫告诉美国...
In other news, Premier Khrushchev told the United...
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
让彼得斯中奖了！
Jean Peters hit the jackpot!
莎莉告诉我 他被转移到拉斯维加斯
Sally told me he was moving to Las Vegas
一会儿 但不结婚
for a while, but not to get married.
而与此同时 他出城
And meanwhile, he's out of town,
而他得到了可怜的弗兰克和莱瓦尔
and he's got poor Frank and Levar
在工作室闭门所有白天和黑夜
cooped up in the studio all day and night.
我要去到明天RKO
I'm gonna go down to RKO tomorrow
并告诉莱瓦尔为什么你不能相信
and tell Levar why you can't believe
什么霍华德•休斯曾经如是说
anything Howard Hughes ever says.
我和霍华德•休斯有它
I've had it with Howard Hughes.
玛米 我忘了什么事我跟你后来赶上
Mamie, I forgot something. I'll catch up with you later.
嘿 玛米
Hey, Mamie.
你好 先生们
Hello, gentlemen.
我不希望有人知道我不是在拉斯维加斯
I don't want anybody knowing I'm not in Las Vegas.
他们不能知道我在洛杉矶
They cannot know I'm in Los Angeles.
我们得到了一些事情赶上
We got some things to catch up on.
只要告诉他叫什么名字
Just tell what's his name,
步行到白宫
to walk over to the White House
贷款副总统的弟弟$ 205,000
and loan the vice president's brother $205,000.
念给我听听我的备忘录的最后一页
Read me back the last page of my memo
我妻子的失踪猫
on my wife's missing cat.
是的 Hughes先生
Yes, Mr. Hughes.
“我已经在拉斯维加斯37小时了
"I have been in Las Vegas for 37 hours now.
“我已经被告知没有发生过
"I have been told there has not been
“进步丝毫
"one iota of progress
“在洛杉矶寻找我妻子的失踪猫
"in Los Angeles in the search for my wife's missing cat.
“我希望有人谁是专家
"I want somebody who is an expert
“在这种类型的动物的方法
"in the ways of animals of this type.
“洛杉矶是不是丛林
"Los Angeles is not the jungle.
“这不是大沼泽地这不是纽约市
"It is not the Everglades. It is not New York City
“在人口密集
"with the dense population.
“如果一个动物园已经失去了一些宝贵的动物
"If a zoo had lost some valuable animal
“在洛杉矶地区
"in the Los Angeles area,
“就不会有25或30人
"there would have been 25 or 30 men
“淘农村
"scouring the countryside,
“男人熟练这种动物的生活习惯和方式
"men skilled in the habits and ways of an animal of this kind
“并会由现在找到了”
"and would have found it by now."
“我觉得有绝对没有理由
"I feel that there is absolutely no reason why
“搜索不应该鼓动
"a search should not have been instigated
“对于这种动物 以任何方式相等
"for this animal, equal in any way
“什么都不会发生
"to what would have happened
“如果一些该死的火车已经在这里打破
"if some damned train had broken down here
“有的豹豹或诸如此类的东西或逃脱
"and some leopard or panther or whatnot had escaped.
“我们绝对没有理由我的资源的人
"There is absolutely no reason why a man of my resources
“而具有我所获得的资源和组织
"and having the resources and organization that I have got,
“有世界上没有该死的理由”
"there is no goddamned reason in the world."
“有很多 很多 很多事情
"There are many, many, many things
“可能已经完成
"that could have been done
“在将近一年半的时间
"in the almost one and a half days
“我一直在拉斯维加斯
"that I have been here in Las Vegas.
“我希望你会读这个七次
"I hope you will read this seven times,
“因为我从来没有什么意思
"because I have never meant anything
“更真诚 比我的意思是这一点
"more sincerely than I mean this.
“签订后 霍华德•休斯河”
"Signed, Howard R. Hughes."
这是26页长 休斯先生
It's 26 pages long, Mr. Hughes.
我们有四个碳副本
We have four carbon copies.
你好？
Hello?
霍华德 我在这里
Howard, I'm here.
- 你要见我 - 我现在已经结婚了 诺亚
- You wanted to see me. - I'm married now, Noah.
你还认为我需要待观察
Do you still think I need to be seen
这些TWA人呢？
by these TWA people?
那么 你就不得不让他们
Well, you're going to have to let them
看你最终 霍华德
look at you eventually, Howard.
承认吧 诺亚
Admit it, Noah.
你不能法律承诺我到精神病院
You can't legally commit me to an insane asylum,
因为我已经结了婚的女人
because I have married a woman
我已经知道并信任多年
that I have known and trusted for years,
而且你也很清楚
and you know very well
她不会让她同意才行
that she would never give her consent to it.
我爱你 诺亚 但你不是我的父亲
I love you, Noah, but you're not my father.
你被开除了
You're fired.
你已经被取代
You've been replaced.
他是幸运有你 弗兰克
He's lucky to have you, Frank.
祝你好运 儿子
Good luck, son.
不要让他开始想你想是他的父亲
Don't let him start to think you're trying to be his father.
副总统的弟弟显然是
The vice president's brother is apparently
不是在华盛顿特区 这个星期
not in Washington, D.C., this week.
我们认为他是在迈阿密
We think he's in Miami.
他将假想...
And he will supposedly...
他的秘书说 他会回来的
His secretary said he'll be back
有时在中间
sometime in the middle
或下周结束
or end of next week.
因此 如果我们需要取得联系 与他或给他任何东西
So if we need to get in touch with him or send him anything,
我们可以做的某个时候它向中部...
we can do it sometime towards the middle...
- 弗兰克 弗兰克 弗兰克 - 是的 Hughes先生？
- Frank, Frank, Frank. - Yes, Mr. Hughes?
他知道我回到了洛杉矶？
Does he know I'm back in Los Angeles?
我不希望有再次打电话给他
I don't wanna have to call him again.
我想香蕉坚果冰淇淋
I want banana nut ice cream.
嘿 打扰一下
Hey. Excuse me.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
这是怎么回事？
What's going on?
- 斯特拉星光！- 你在说什么？
- Stella Starlight! - What are you talking about?
斯特拉星光是真的 真的很愚蠢的标题
Stella Starlight is a really, really stupid title
一个真正愚蠢的电影
for a really stupid movie.
但几乎没有愚蠢的我
But not nearly as stupid as I am
- 对于想他会永远做它- 你在说什么？
- for thinking he'd ever make it. - What are you talking about?
首先 他给了我一个关于我是多么伟大的大量垃圾
First, he gives me a lot of junk about how great I am.
而现在 我不能让他在手机上
And now I can't get him on the phone.
他甚至还没有费心去看看我的愚蠢试镜！
He hasn't even bothered to look at my stupid screen test!
- 等一下 - 等待什么时间吗？
- Wait a minute. - Wait a minute for what?
- 等一下 - 霍华德•休斯？
- Wait a minute. - Howard Hughes?
那是你在等待谁？
Is that who you're waiting for?
我想你应该花一些时间
I think you should take some time.
也许不要试图劝我在我的职业生涯
And maybe don't try to advise me on my career.
我怎么能建议你在你的职业生涯？
How could I advise you on your career?
我不知道发生了什么事情在你的生活或者
I have no idea what's going on in your life or where
你得到从你的建议而且我不问了
you're getting your advice from. And I'm not asking.
我不要求你的戒指
I'm not asking about your ring.
我不要求...
I'm not asking...
福布斯牧师 香蕉坚果
Reverend Forbes, banana nut.
你知道 我不知道我是否还在她得到了一个镜头
You know, I don't know if I still got a shot at her.
但是 如果有人做 相信我
But if anybody does, trust me,
这是弗雷斯诺的牧师弗兰克•福布斯
it's the Reverend Frank Forbes of Fresno.
停止
Stop.
休斯先生 我想 也许现在是一个好时机
Mr. Hughes, I think maybe now is a good time
对付 我跟你说话有关的种植面积
to deal with the acreage that I spoke to you about
峡谷关闭穆赫兰道我有一个计划
the canyon off Mulholland Drive. I've got a plan.
郊区发展的时机已经到来
The time for suburban development has come.
它的时代已经到来......而且我...
Its time has come... And, and...
穆赫兰峡谷会是黄金
Mulholland Canyon is gonna be gold.
你知道什么雨果
And you know what Victor Hugo
曾经有人说？“没有什么如此强大
once said? "There's nothing so powerful
“作为一种想法
"as an idea whose time
“来了”
"has come."
我想刚才你开车
I would like to just drive you
- 在那里明天告诉你 - 霍华德 这是鲍勃•马耶
- out there tomorrow and show you. - Howard, it's Bob Maheu.
在我的第一天作为新的CEO
On my first day as your new CEO,
我必须告诉你 如果你不
I must tell you that if you don't
让这些人从TWA看到你
let these people from TWA see you,
它们可以让你被他们在法庭上看到
they can make you be seen by them in court.
鲍勃鲍勃 鲍勃
Bob. Bob, Bob.
没有人让我在任何地方看到
Nobody makes me be seen anywhere.
你明白了吗？
You got that?
但是 我...
However, I am...
我今晚让你见过
I am making you be seen tonight
在拉斯维加斯 内华达州 与我们的全体工作人员
in Las Vegas, Nevada, with our entire staff.
我们都是要去那里 今晚我们都在飞翔
We're all gonna be there, we're all flyin' in tonight.
我们要搬到内华达州你想知道为什么吗？
We're moving to Nevada. You wanna know why?
因为我卖TWA
Because I am selling TWA.
销售TWA？
Selling TWA?
还有在内华达州 弗兰克没有州税
There's no state tax in Nevada, Frank.
霍华德？
Howard?
如果你还是怕的飞翔“......
And if you're still afraid of flyin'...
霍华德？
Howard?
......你知道 你最好在上车不久
...you know, you better get in the car soon,
因为它是一个三小时47分钟的车程
because it's a three hour and 47 minute drive.
霍华德？
Howard?
那是香蕉坚果？
Is that banana nut?
呃...
Uh...
香蕉坚果 先生 是啊
Banana nut, sir. Yeah.
♪某处♪
♪ Somewhere ♪
♪除了海♪
♪ Beyond the sea ♪
♪某处等着我♪
♪ Somewhere waiting for me ♪
♪我的爱人站在金色的沙滩上♪
♪ My lover stands on golden sands ♪
主席先生
Mr. President,
我知道你知道有多好
I know how well you understand
有没有谁做过超过我
that there is no one who has done more than I have
摆脱共产党的好莱坞
to rid Hollywood of communists.
并请允许我澄清一下 一次
And please allow me to clarify, once more,
极端危险所有美国人
the extreme danger all Americans
将面临在附近居住的一个核试验基地的任何地方
will face in living anywhere near a nuclear test site.
真诚的 霍华德•休斯河
Sincerely, Howard R. Hughes.
猫王 帕特•布恩 弗兰基的Avalon 鲍比达林
Elvis Presley, Pat Boone, Frankie Avalon, Bobby Darin.
我的意思是 你认为什么样的鲍比达林一个人做的东西
I mean, what do you think a guy like Bobby Darin makes on something
像“飞越情海”？
like "Beyond The Sea"?
坦率地说 最近怎么回事
Frank, how's it going on
香蕉坚果冰淇淋面前？
the banana nut ice cream front?
该公司绝对不会做它了
The company's definitely not making it anymore.
但好消息是我们所在
But the good news is we located
最后一批350加仑
the last batch, 350 gallons.
而且公司是非常合作
And the company's being very cooperative.
让我们买它
Let's buy it.
该公司的非卖品 先生
The company's not for sale, sir.
冰淇淋！购买这一切
The ice cream! Buy all of it.
- 它是如何来的？ - 通过冷藏车
- How does it get here? - By refrigerated truck.
那么 我们为什么不靠谱吗？
Well, why don't we fly it in?
冰淇淋并不在飞机上以及旅行
Ice cream does not travel well on airplanes.
我们为什么不寻找到一个...
Why don't we look into a...
- ...冷藏车？ - 这是一个好主意 先生
- ...refrigerated truck? - That's a great idea, sir.
休斯先生 我发现越来越多的税收优惠
Mr. Hughes, I'm finding more and more tax advantages
在内华达州购买了房地产
for buying up real estate in Nevada.
随着加速折旧 你只是在酒店一样多
With accelerated depreciation, you get just as much on hotels
- 因为你会在 在购物中心 - 这是白宫的一次
- as you would on, on shopping centers. - It's the White House again.
休斯先生 白宫再次调用...
Mr. Hughes, the White House is calling again...
我想香蕉坚果冰淇淋！
I want banana nut ice cream!
我在沙漠中！
I am in the middle of a desert!
你是不是和我一起在沙漠里？
Are you not in the desert with me?
这难道不是不够热的沙漠？
Is it not hot enough for the desert?
我在哪里可以把冰淇淋350加仑 是吧？
Where do I put 350 gallons of ice cream, huh?
同样的味道！
The same flavor!
所有这一切都为香蕉坚果！
All of it is banana nut!
所有这一切都为香蕉坚果！卡洛斯？
All of it is banana nut! Carlos?
坦率地说 我们已经在这里等了六个星期
Frank, we've been waiting here for six weeks.
我是他的首席执行官
I am his chief executive officer.
我一定要和他见面
I have to meet him.
我明白了 马耶先生
I understand, Mr. Maheu.
当然 你说得对在加利福尼亚州 流产的...
Of course, you're right. In California, abortion's...
......不合法的
...not legal.
你可能会想更多地考虑整个事情
You might wanna give the whole thing more thought.
♪铃儿响叮当♪
♪ Jingle bells ♪
♪丁当一路... ♪
♪ Jingle all the way... ♪
霍华德 我认为我们应该满足
Howard, I think we should meet.
教育部达利兹说他需要你改变地板
Moe Dalitz says he needs you to change floors.
他们拥有的酒店
They own the hotel.
暴徒是没时间跟你上当
The mob is nothing to be fooled with.
我们可以请见面？
Can we please meet?
你看 你问这个低劣的小流氓黑手党
Look, you ask that shitty little Mafia hoodlum
他是多么想为酒店
how much he wants for the hotel
并说“是”的情况 他在星期四出去了
and say "yes" on the condition he's out by Thursday.
有没有必要为你或任何人看到我
There is no need for you or anyone else to see me.
霍华德我觉得我必须告诉你
Howard. I feel I must advise you
你仍可以在法庭上可以看出
that you can still be made to be seen in court
为了抵御指控
in order to defend against charges
你管理不善TWA
that you mismanaged TWA.
这不是真的 这不是真的
That's not true. That's not true.
我也发现很难
I'm also finding it very difficult
运行你的整个操作
to run your entire operation
当我从来不曾真正见过你
when I've never, ever actually seen you.
我的意思是 在肉体
I mean, in the flesh.
你是否意识到这一点 霍华德？
Do you realize that, Howard?
那我从未见过你？
That I've never actually seen you?
霍华德？
Howard?
鲍勃？如果你是真正看到我
Bob? If you were to actually see me
你不能代表我在我需要的方式
you could not represent me in the way that I need to be.
你是我的首席执行官
You are my chief executive officer,
你不是我的父亲
you are not my father.
好了 这是什么？
Okay, what's this?
这是斯托弗冷冻火鸡晚餐 先生
It's Stouffer frozen turkey dinner, sir.
好吧 我希望你能通知斯托弗公司
Okay, well, I want you to notify the Stouffer company
去除火鸡的黑肉
to remove the dark meat of the turkey
从冷冻火鸡晚餐
from the turkey frozen dinner.
- 香蕉坚果？ - 香蕉坚果 先生
- Banana nut? - Banana nut, sir.
忘记香蕉坚果！
Forget banana nut!
好的 莱瓦尔！
Okay. Levar!
没有更多的香蕉坚果冰淇淋你明白了吗？
No more banana nut ice cream. You got that?
没有更多的香蕉坚果冰淇淋从现在开始...
No more banana nut ice cream. From now on...
我想法国香草
I want French vanilla.
他妈的 我现在想的法国香草
Goddamn it. I want French vanilla now.
我要你给我马耶的那时间表
I want you to bring me that schedule of Maheu's
因为我想知道到底
because I wanna know exactly
什么是那个混蛋在干什么
what that son of a bitch is doing.
休斯先生 玛拉马布里刚刚进来了
Mr. Hughes, Marla Mabrey has just come in.
我把她放在免提房间
I put her in the speakerphone room.
我告诉她你是不可用的 先生？
Shall I tell her you're unavailable, sir?
弗兰克 处理这个问题 你愿意吗？
Frank, handle this, will you?
跟她谈谈
Go talk to her.
告诉她 我只是没有看到人
Tell her I'm just not seeing people.
我想法国香草从现在开始！
I want French vanilla from now on!
立即法国香草
French vanilla immediately.
嗨
Hi.
我能为你做什么？
What can I do for you?
这是我的职业生涯中 不是你的
It's my career, not yours.
您还可以通过接受 帮助
And you can help by accepting that.
这真的不关你 弗兰克
It's really none of your business, Frank.
好的
Okay.
但是你可以告诉你的老板
But you can tell your boss
我觉得这只是我与他会见权
I feel it's only right that I meet with him
之前采取任何行动
before taking any action.
我不知道 你永远不会看着她试镜
I don't know. You never looked at her screen test.
她可能有新的人谁是建议她
She might have someone new who's advising her.
谁？一个代理？律师？什么？
Who? An agent? Lawyer? What?
你听说过她可能会参与人？
Have you heard she might be involved with somebody?
我听说过什么！ 一世...
I've heard nothing! I...
没关系 你先走 我会和她谈谈
Never mind. You go ahead. I'll talk to her.
是的先生
Yes, sir.
玛拉？你是 你在那里 玛拉？
Marla? Are you, are you there, Marla?
你在房间里？
Are you in the room?
我不能这样做
I can't do this
在电话里 霍华德
on the telephone, Howard.
我没有看到人
I'm not seeing people.
这是我们不打算在发生
Something we didn't plan on has happened.
你最好拿起电话 玛拉
You better pick up the phone, Marla.
我们应该更加小心
We should have been more careful.
从单一的遭遇 玛拉？从一次？
From a single encounter, Marla? From one time?
你真的以为我会相信吗？
Do you really expect me to believe that?
我很惊讶
I'm surprised.
我没想到你是怎样的一个人
I didn't think you were that kind of a person.
多少钱你找谁？
How much money are you looking for?
嘿 香草和法国香草 是一回事吗？
Hey, is vanilla and French vanilla, is it the same thing?
耶耶耶
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
是的 这是一样的吗？我要去检查就可以了
Yes, it's the same? I'm gonna go check on it.
你表现得疯了
You're acting crazy.
我更了解比你想我做的生意
I know more about the business than you think I do.
哦 你的未来 弗兰克那些大交易？
Oh, all those big deals in your future, Frank?
你最好让他们在写作
You better get them in writing.
我不需要他们的写作
I don't need them in writing.
嗯 这是正确的“因为你信任他
Well, that's right. 'Cause you trust him.
他甚至不会与妻子见面
He won't even meet with his wife.
- 幸运的女人 - 他不会让任何人看他
- Lucky woman. - He won't let anybody look at him.
- 哦 他是对的！ - 没有理由...
- Oh, well, he's right! - There's no reason...
他是对的因为他们可能会看到他到底是什么
He's right. Because they might see exactly what he is,
寒冷 肮脏 极端自私 老假
a cold, sleazy, egomaniacal, old fake
不值得与满足
not worth meeting with.
你想有会议或拍电影？
You wanna have meetings or make movies?
他们得到了球员的名字正在做你在做什么 弗兰克
They got names for guys that are doing what you're doing, Frank.
谁你以为你在跟谁说话？
Who do you think you're talking to?
我想我说的就是有人说售罄
I think I'm talking to somebody that sold out
你可以告诉你卖完了的家伙
and you can tell the guy that you sold out to
我是再也不会回到那个愚蠢的房子！
that I'm never going back to that stupid house!
他可以在里面扔什么的了
And he can throw whatever's in it away.
而你想回家给你的未婚妻
And that you wanna go home to your fiancée
并获得合法结婚！
and get legally married!
你真的认为你与霍华德•休斯去什么地方？
Do you actually think that you're going somewhere with Howard Hughes?
你甚至害怕坐上他的飞机！
You're even scared to get on his plane!
- 好吧 只是... - 不要是物理与我 谢了！
- Okay, just... - Don't be physical with me, Frank!
谁到底是通知您现在...
Whoever the hell is advising you right now...
你知道 这不关你现在谁的劝告我！
You know, it's none of your business who's advising me now!
你需要有人谁现在是通知您！
You need someone who's advising you now!
继续前进 弗兰克 继续前进！我有！
To move on, Frank, move on! I have!
- 你介意我说话吗？- 离开这里！
- Do you mind if I speak? - Get out of here!
没有 因为没有什么可说的！
No, because there's nothing left to say!
如果你打电话给我 我也不会和你说话
And if you call me, I won't talk to you.
所以 善待我的隐私与尊重！
So kindly treat my privacy with respect!
尊重？
Respect?
回到你那该死的神秘人
Go back to your goddamn mystery man,
与您的隐私和环
with your privacy and your rings
不要担心我曾经打电话给你
and don't worry about me ever calling you.
相信我 我永远也不会！
Believe me, I never will!
纳丁 谁给那马耶没告诉我？
Nadine, who called that Maheu didn't tell me about?
今天？ 美国联邦航空局的主席
Today? The chairman of the FAA,
国防部副部长的
the Under Secretary of Defense,
财政部长
the Treasury secretary,
有人从空中交通管制员的工会
someone from the air traffic controller's union,
从AFL-CIO的人
and a man from the AFL-CIO.
好吧 你看 我们留下了婊子马耶那儿子
All right, look, we're leaving that son of a bitch Maheu
独自一人在拉斯维加斯今晚
alone in Vegas tonight.
没有人告诉他吧！他完成了他被解雇了！
Nobody tells him about it! He's finished. He's fired!
我们要尼加拉瓜
We're going to Nicaragua.
这不是世界上唯一的地方不含税！
This isn't the only place in the world without taxes!
把我的飞行员夹克
Get me my pilot's jacket.
好吧 来吧 来吧 我们走吧 来吧！
All right, come on, come on. Let's go. Come on!
从厨房走了
Going through the kitchen now.
这一切都取决于我没有东西买了
It's all up to me. Nothing gets bought,
没有东西没有我出售
nothing gets sold without me.
对于所有的实际目的 我是霍华德•休斯
For all practical purposes, I am Howard Hughes.
来吧 弗兰克得到失控的汽车
Come on, Frank. Get outta the car.
没有什么可害怕的
There's nothing to be afraid of.
来吧！
Come on!
弗兰克 你可以做到这一点 来吧 飞行可以很有趣
Frank, you can do this. Come on. Flying can be fun.
我想我已经准备好了
I think I'm ready.
好吧 卡比 它的时候我再次做到这一点
Okay, Cappy, it's about time I did this again.
先生们 我终于要去做些什么
Gentlemen, I am finally gonna do something
我没有太久完成
that I haven't done for far too long.
时间太长了
Far too long.
卡比 这是弗兰克这里的第一个乘坐飞机
Cappy, this is Frank here's first plane ride.
我想使它令人难忘
I wanna make it memorable.
- 一切都准备好了吗？- 是的先生
- Everything ready? - Yes, sir.
开始了
Here we go.
我们得到了香蕉坚果？
We got banana nut?
我们有没有...
Have we...
- 呃 - 一品脱半 先生
- Uh... - A pint and a half, sir.
品脱半
Pint and a half.
最后！ 它已经太久太久！
Finally! It's been far too long!
时间太长了
Far too long.
汤匙
Spoons.
索摩查总统登上来了！
President Somoza is coming aboard!
休斯先生！
Mr. Hughes!
欢迎来到尼加拉瓜
Welcome to Nicaragua.
你看起来不可思议！
You look incredible!
- 你看起来很棒 - 谢谢 你也是
- You look wonderful. - Thank you. So do you.
- 你有没有老化 - 谢谢
- You have not aged. - Thank you.
我想知道你在做什么？
I wanna know what you're doing in...
有你的一个重要的信息
There's an important message for you.
“美国联邦法院今天决定...
"The United States Federal Court decided today...
“......在TWA的情况下...
"...in the case of TWA...
“...的6.45亿$的判决
"...a judgment of $645 million
“对付霍华德•休斯...
"against Howard Hughes...
“......谁拒绝出庭”
"...who refused to appear."
这不可能是好的
This cannot be good.
他们认为我必须卖掉
They think I'll have to sell
休斯工具公司支付呢？
the Hughes Tool Company to pay it?
我永远不会卖掉我爸爸的公司
I'll never sell my daddy's company.
我爸爸会说这是时间打电话
My daddy would say it's time to call
雷蒙德•霍利迪在休斯顿了
Raymond Holliday down in Houston.
让他到这里来了
Get him to come down here.
所以...
So...
我只是想让你知道
I just want you to know
我不认为你正在做错误的事情
I don't think you're doing the wrong thing.
而且我很放心
And I am so relieved
你没有要回好莱坞
that you're not going back to Hollywood.
妈妈 我还没有告诉这个另一种活的灵魂
Mom, I haven't told another living soul about this.
医生钻石是个好人
Doctor Diamond is a good man,
他的到来在上周日
and he's coming in on a Sunday.
那么 我们走吧？
So, shall we go?
现在 当你10岁时
Now, when you were 10 years old,
当你使用下来到你爸爸的工厂......
when you used to come down to your daddy's factory...
雷蒙德 我爸爸总是信任我
Raymond, my daddy always trusted me
为处理后事
to take care of things.
现在 试图照顾休斯工具公司
Now, trying to take care of the Hughes Tool Company
在这样的时刻
at a time like this.
这就像试图把我的爸爸照顾
That's like trying to take care of my daddy.
你不是你爸爸的爸爸 霍华德
You're not your daddy's father, Howard.
你爸爸死了
Your daddy's dead.
不 他不是
No, he's not.
他在我的DNA
He's in my DNA.
我的天！
Oh, Lord!
你知道 你是怎么死的 太
You know, you're gonna die, too.
谁你要离开它？谁的DNA你会在？
Who you gonna leave it to? Whose DNA you gonna be in?
在我看来 如果你现在不签字
In my opinion, if you don't sign it now,
他们该怎么办 他们说了什么
they're gonna do what they said.
他们会撤回要约收购该死的公司
They're gonna withdraw the offer to buy the damn company.
所以 如果我签这个东西 他们会依旧保持
So, if I sign this thing, would they still keep
对公司休斯的名字吗？
the Hughes name on the company?
你不使用一个名称 霍华德钻探石油
You don't drill for oil with a name, Howard.
你知道吗 我打算做一个小的飞翔“
You know, I'm planning on doing a little flyin'.
你要来？
Do you wanna come?
- 做一个小飞翔？ - 嗯
- Do a little flyin'? - Hmm.
什么？
What?
我只是不知道...
I'm just not sure...
......你应该“关于飞翔了 霍华德要想着
...you ought to be thinkin' about flyin' anymore, Howard.
在弗兰克来吧
Come on in, Frank.
好的 请把这个交给的绅士
Okay. Please give this to the gentleman, and
告诉他 我问他
tell him that I have asked him
请考虑
to please consider
保持对公司我父亲的名字
keeping my father's name on the company.
这是签署
This is signed.
休斯先生已经要求你考虑保留
Mr. Hughes has asked you to consider keeping
他父亲的名字上了公司
his father's name on the company.
我注意到你不说恩典了
I notice you don't say grace anymore.
我不是说是负面的 但做我们的生活
I don't mean to be negative, but do we live
尼加拉瓜现在呢？
in Nicaragua now?
虽然 我还挺越来越喜欢马那瓜
Although, I am kinda getting to like Managua.
波 弗兰克
Wave, Frank.
喔让我们继续下去
Whoo. Let's keep it going.
别担心 别担心！
Don't worry, don't worry!
我知道如何处理地震！
I know how to handle earthquakes!
我们要去伦敦
We're going to London.
退房的税收设置 弗兰克 给我买点儿可待因
Check out the tax setup, Frank, and get me some codeine.
弗吉尼亚大学是怎么回事男女同校
The University of Virginia's going coed.
他们终于让女性
They're finally letting women in
所以我甚至可能去获得博士学位
so I might even go for a doctorate
做音乐我的论文
and do my dissertation on music.
对你有好处
Good for you.
谢谢你不扔我的东西拿走 纳丁
Thanks for not throwing my things away, Nadine.
我不知道从哪里发送
I had no idea where to send them.
我们在哪里叫你在弗吉尼亚州？
Where do we call you in Virginia?
也许这是更好 如果我给你打电话
Maybe it's better if I call you.
因此 百分比表示
Therefore, the percentages noted
在列分别的百分比...
in the column were percentage of...
坦率地说 我们已经在伦敦没有乐趣太长
Frank, we've been in London too long with no fun.
我希望你在盖特威克机场45分钟
I want you at the Gatwick Airport in 45 minutes
在DC-3
in the DC-3.
给男人一些信贷他知道他不能飞
Give the man some credit. He knows he can't fly.
休斯先生！
Mr. Hughes!
很高兴终于见到你的人 先生 最后！
So happy to finally meet you in person, sir. At last!
我敢肯定 你不需要介绍的DC-3这个
I'm sure you need no introduction to the DC-3. This one,
当然 配有
of course, is equipped with
普拉特＆惠特尼R-1830双黄蜂发动机
the Pratt & Whitney R-1830 Twin Wasp engines,
- 这对提高... - 我所知道的DC-3非常好
- which improve... - I know the DC-3 very well.
嗯...
Um...
当然 在这想了原有的旋风787-9的改善
Certainly an improvement over the original Cyclone 9s which were wanting
- 在老魅力部门 - 在哪里 先生们？
- in the old oomph department. - Where to, gentlemen?
我们去哪里？
Where do we go?
我不知道 先生如果我们向东
I don't know, sir. If we are heading east,
那将是法国北部 比利时可能
then that would be northern France, possibly Belgium.
你觉得呢 联队司令？比利时华夫饼？
What do you think, wing commander? Belgian waffles?
它是如何听起来？
How does it sound?
呃 我不知道
Uh, I don't know.
好吧 没关系 你想要一个鸡肉三明治？
All right, never mind. You want a chicken sandwich?
- 不饿- 不饿好的
- Not hungry. - Not hungry. Okay.
你呢？ 你想要一个鸡肉三明治？
How about you? Do you want a chicken sandwich?
- 不 谢谢 - 我有三个
- No, thank you. - I got three.
- 我很好刚吃过 - 没有？
- I'm fine. Just eaten. - No?
你知道吗 你是20％不太可能停电
Did you know that you're 20% less likely to black out
潜水过程中 当你我的年龄？
during a dive when you're my age?
因为动脉是那样广泛
Because the arteries are less expansive.
不 我不知道 先生
No, I didn't know it, sir.
记住
Remember that.
- 值得期待的东西 - 是的！
- Something to look forward to. - Yes!
好了 我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
我想我们可能有一个门还开着
I think we may have a door still open.
放松！我喜欢这样！只是关闭驾驶舱
Relax! I like it like that! Just close the cockpit.
先生们 你们是没见过没什么呢
Gentlemen, you ain't seen nothin' yet.
你知道 行铝乔森用用
You know that line Al Jolson used to use,
“你是不是听到了什么”没有“？
"You ain't heard nothin' yet"?
第一次 他曾经唱了 我看见了他
First time he ever sang it, I saw him
楼上的屋顶上
upstairs on the roof
在阿姆斯特丹剧院而正是
at the Amsterdam Theatre. And it was
一个大的慈善演出
a big charity show.
每个人的大明星 大明星 乔森说
Everybody's big stars, big stars, and Jolson says,
“我要关闭显示
"I gotta close the show,
“因为我是世界上最伟大的艺人
"because I'm the world's greatest entertainer
“没有人 但没有人 遵循乔森”
"and nobody, but nobody, follows Jolson."
好了 大家说
Well, everybody said,
“好吧 乔森 你是最伟大的
"Okay, Jolson, you're the greatest.
“你关闭显示”
"You close the show."
现在只有一个问题 但
There was only one problem though.
乔森不知道他是谁之后
Jolson didn't know who he was following.
卡鲁索
Caruso.
他得起床卡鲁索之后唱歌
He's gotta get up and sing after Enrico Caruso,
世界上最伟大的声音！ 哈！
the world's greatest voice! Ha!
因此 卡鲁索出来 他唱意大利语
So, Caruso comes out, he's singing in Italian.
观众们只是去疯狂
The audience just goes crazy.
他们发疯
They go crazy.
他们是在他们的脚欢呼
They're on their feet cheering.
他们不会坐下来 他们欢呼！
They won't sit down, they're cheering!
卡鲁索熄灭
Caruso goes off,
乔森出来
Jolson comes out.
但是 他不能让他们闭嘴
But he can't get them to shut up,
因为他们想要更多的卡鲁索
because they want more Caruso.
最后乔森关闭它们
And finally Jolson shuts them up.
他让他们坐下来时 他说 那是
He makes them sit down and that's when he says it.
他说 “你知道 你是不是听到什么呢！”
He says, "You know, you ain't heard nothing yet!"
“你是不是听到什么呢！”
"You ain't heard nothing yet!"
♪这是真的 他们说的是什么迪克西♪
♪ Is it true what they say about Dixie ♪
♪是否阳光照耀真的所有的时间？♪
♪ Does the sun really shine all the time? ♪
♪做甜木兰开花♪
♪ Do the sweet magnolias blossom ♪
♪圆大家的门吗？♪
♪ Round everybody's door? ♪
♪做乡亲继续吃负鼠 直到他们不能吃没有更多？♪
♪ Do folks keep eating possum 'til they can't eat no more? ♪
♪这是真的 他们说的是什么斯瓦尼？♪
♪ Is it true what they say about Swanee? ♪
♪是一个梦想由流♪
♪ Is a dream by that stream ♪
♪那么崇高？♪
♪ So sublime? ♪
♪难道他们笑 做自己爱就像他们在所有的歌曲说的？♪
♪ Do they laugh, do they love like they say in all the song? ♪
♪如果这是真的 这是属于我的地方♪
♪ If it's true, that's where I belong ♪
♪斯瓦尼♪
♪ Swanee ♪
看看这个
Take a look at this.
♪我如何爱你 我多么爱你♪
♪ How I love ya, how I love ya ♪
♪我亲爱的老斯瓦尼♪
♪ My dear old Swanee ♪
♪我想给这个世界是♪
♪ I'd give the world to be ♪
♪其中在DIXIE乡亲♪
♪ Among the folks in D-I-X-I-E ♪
♪虽然我的妈咪的等着我 祈祷'我♪
♪ Even though my mammy's waitin' for me, prayin' for me ♪
嘿嘿 谢了！
Hey, Frank!
飞翔真的让一个人一个机会
Flyin' really gives a guy a chance
做一些思考 不是吗？
to do some thinking, doesn't it?
你知道我在想什么 弗兰克？
You know what I'm thinking, Frank?
我在想 是时候让我买
I am thinking that it's time for me to buy
乘坐泛美航空公司！
Pan American Airlines!
你是不是听到了什么'呢！
You ain't heard nothin' yet!
嘿 你布莱恩'？回到这来
Hey, where you goin'? Come back here.
嗯 告诉酒店保安告诉妈妈...
Well, tell hotel security to tell the mother...
是的 有三个人他们都在这里
Yes, there's three of them. They're all up here.
哇 哇 哇
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
走这条路
Go this way.
我不知道他们是怎么进去的
I have no idea how they got in.
来吧 孩子 请！
Come on, kid. Please!
你得离开这里小子
You gotta get out of here. Kid.
我知道你在哪里 孩子请出来
I know where you are, kid. Please come out.
请 你妈妈正等着你
Please. Your mother is waiting for you.
休斯先生！
Mr. Hughes!
Hughes先生
Mr. Hughes,
我们有好消息！
we have wonderful news!
上诉法院已推翻了TWA判断
The court of appeals has reversed the TWA judgment.
你得到的钱全部回来了！
You get all the money back!
莱瓦尔！你居然这么鸟右脑
Levar! Are you actually so bird-brained
你以为我不知道吗？
you think I didn't know that?
我起床比你早做
I get up earlier than you do.
嘿 看看你
Hey, look at you.
- 你叫什么名字？ - 嗨
- What's your name? - Hi.
- 汤米 - 你想一些冰淇淋吗？
- Tommy. - Would you like some ice cream?
这将会是对你有好处！来吧 让我们去！
It'd be good for you! Come on, let's go!
来吧 孩子我们得走了
Come on, kid. We gotta go.
但他可能会喜欢冰淇淋
But he might like some ice cream.
那么 他的母亲很不高兴
Well, his mother is very upset.
为什么你跟他的母亲呢？他也许是想冰淇淋
Why did you talk to his mother? He might have wanted ice cream.
在大厅或事端等待了
Wait out in the hall or somethin'.
为什么你跟他的母亲呢？
Why did you talk to his mother?
我没有跟母亲我跟安全性
I didn't talk to the mother. I talked to security.
你总是说让孩子出去
You always say to keep kids out.
为什么你跟安全性？
Why did you talk to security?
因为这是我的工作！
Because that's my job!
- 那是你的工作吗？ - 是的！
- That is your job? - Yes!
你告诉我你的工作是什么？
You're telling me what your job is?
是! 这是我的工作！
Yes! That is my job!
你的任务是告诉我你的工作是什么！
Your job is to tell me what your job is!
- 你聋了吗？- 什么？
- Are you deaf? - What?
你是聋子你是聋子！而你是老了
You are deaf. You're deaf! And you're old.
你很老了 你很聋子！
You're very old, and you're very deaf!
你叫我老聋？
You calling me old and deaf?
你是聋子 你就老了！而且很聋 很老！
You're deaf, and you're old! And very deaf, and very old!
你不知道你的工作是什么
You do not know what your job is.
不 我知道我的工作是什么！你不知道我的工作是什么！
No, I know what my job is! You do not know what my job is!
你不知道你的工作是什么！
You don't know what your job is!
我知道我的工作！我知道我的工作！
I know my job! I know my job!
- 你知道你的工作是什么？ - 我知道我的工作是什么！
- You know what your job is? - I know what my job is!
你知道 这是“是”
You know, it's "was."
- 是 - 是
- Is. - Was.
- 是 是的 是的 - 是 是的
- Is. Is. Is. - Was. Was.
- 是？ - 不 是
- Was? - No, was.
- 是？ - 是那是你的工作
- Was? - Was. That was your job.
出去
Get out.
爵士 母亲很不高兴
Sir, the mother's very upset.
出去
Get out.
以14天就穆赫兰峡谷的决定
Take 14 days to make a decision on Mulholland Canyon.
莱瓦尔和我会做到这一点不管你做不做
Levar and I are gonna do it whether you do it or not.
我知道这很难让你信任的人
I know it's hard for you to trust people,
但莱瓦尔是为你加油 无论你如何得到坚果
but Levar is rooting for you no matter how nutty you get.
这将是我们在与贵公司的一大优势
It would be a big advantage for us to be in business with you,
但它可能会为你在事业与我们的一大优势
but it might be a big advantage for you to be in business with us.
如果你决定不
If you decide not to,
我只能恭敬地接受你的决定 辞职
I can only respectfully accept your decision and resign.
你有没有意识到
Do you realize
你吸毒不仅会让你更加便秘
that your drug addiction not only makes you more constipated,
这会让你更疯狂？
it makes you crazier?
但是 由于没有谁给你的作品 包括我在内
But since no one who works for you, including me,
会对自己的工作就行了
will put their job on the line
要尽量保持你杀死自己
to try to keep you from killing yourself,
那么也许你的财富
then maybe your wealth
并不总是对你的健康是最好的事情
isn't always the best thing for your health.
弗兰克 为什么你从不谈论你的爸爸？
Frank, how come you never talk about your daddy?
什么？
What?
你永远不谈论你的爸爸 怎么来的？
You never talk about your daddy. How come?
我总是告诉我的母亲 我是多么爱她 但我......
I could always tell my mother how much I loved her, but I...
我不能告诉我的爸爸是好...
I couldn't tell my daddy that well...
我不知道
I don't know.
但是 我想念我的爸爸
But I miss my daddy.
我希望我可以和他谈谈
I wish I could just talk to him.
你知道 我想我从未有过一个孩子
You know, I think I never had a kid
因为我怕会让我觉得自己老了
because I was afraid that would make me feel old.
还记得我们出去夜
Remember the night we went out to
坐着看飞机 并有汉堡包 你知道吗？
sit and look at the plane, and had the burgers, you know?
这是一个汉堡包地狱
It was a hell of a hamburger.
你还相信
Do you still believe in
什么教堂告诉你要相信
what the church tells you to believe,
喜欢...
like...
在天堂和...
In heaven and...
我不知道 Hughes先生
I don't know, Mr. Hughes.
是啊 我不是
Yeah, me either.
我只是...
I just...
我不想做一个人做一探究竟
I don't wanna do what a person has to do to find out.
嗯...
Um...
好吧 你看 我会做穆赫兰道峡谷和你在一起
All right, look, I'll do Mulholland Canyon with you.
我会做的很大但是我刚刚......在一个条件
And I'll do it big. But I just got... Under one condition.
从现在开始
From now on,
你会打电话给我霍华德？
will you call me Howard?
是啊！
Yeah!
我们正站在
We are standing by
从传说中的一个电话
for a telephone call from legendary
亿万富翁霍华德•休斯 这可能揭穿一个作家的说法...
billionaire Howard Hughes, which could debunk a writer's claim...
前面提到的作家理查德•Miskin
The writer that was mentioned earlier, Richard Miskin,
声称已经获得霍华德•休斯
claims to have had access to Howard Hughes.
在这段时间 他说:
And during that time, he says
休斯不记得任何事情
that Hughes could not remember anything,
是语无伦次 无法
was incoherent, and unable
发挥作用
to function.
这休斯痴呆的永久状态
And that Hughes is in a permanent state of dementia.
霍华德•休斯的位置
The location of Howard Hughes
仍是一个谜给我们
is still a complete mystery to us.
这将是休斯的一大难题...
It will be a major problem for Hughes...
- 是啊 - ......如果他不给我们打电话
- Yeah. - ...if he doesn't call us
由休斯组织承诺
as promised by the Hughes organization,
和自己辩护
and defend himself against
在Miskin的书的指控
the charges in Miskin's book.
一个谁在帮助开拓者...
One of the pioneers who helped in...
霍华德
Howard.
...是霍华德•休斯
...was Howard Hughes.
他是最有影响力的人之一
He's one of the most influential individuals
最后四分之一世纪
of the last quarter century.
嗯 如果她甚至不会告诉你她的名字......
Well, if she won't even tell you her name...
休斯浪漫与
Hughes was romantically linked
多年来几个年轻女演员...
to several young actresses over the years...
是啊
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
......制造25百万美元的飞行船
...manufactured a 25 million dollar flying boat.
同时 我们被告知笔者
Meanwhile, we're told that the writer,
理查德Miskin 可以给我们很快说话
Richard Miskin, may speak to us soon.
她没事的 伙计们我懂了
She's okay, guys. I got this.
这些家伙做他们的工作
These guys do their job.
是啊 嗯...
Yeah, well...
他们是新的
They're new.
你为什么不告诉任何人你是谁？
Why didn't you tell anybody who you were?
好了 最后一次谈话 我与霍华德
Well, the last conversation I had with Howard
是不是很愉快
wasn't very pleasant.
我有事要告诉他 他会谈到记者面前
I have something to tell him before he talks to the press.
马特？
Matt?
马特 这是莱瓦尔莱瓦尔 这是马特
Matt, this is Levar. Levar, this is Matt.
- 嗨 - 你好 马特
- Hi. - Hello, Matt.
嗨
Hi.
我们这里有这本书 理查德Miskin的作家
We have here the writer of the book, Richard Miskin.
Miskin先生 休斯的人说你的书是假的
Mr. Miskin, Hughes' people say your book is a fake.
他从未见过 甚至跟你说话
That he has never met or even spoken with you.
我不认为你会听到休斯先生说
I don't think you'll hear Mr. Hughes say that
或其他任何东西了
or anything else much.
我不认为你会从他的来信
I don't think you're going to be hearing from him.
我怀疑他甚至记得这本书
I doubt he even remembers the book.
让我再次问你...
Let me ask you again...
先生 霍华德•休斯是一个不安的生物
Sir, Howard Hughes is a disturbed creature.
而我的心脏出去给他
And my heart goes out to him.
但如果是在他脆弱的回忆
But if it is upon his flimsy recollection
你正在你的铰报告文学
that you're hinging your reportage,
那么祝你好运
then good luck to you.
这就是我要说的
That's all I have to say.
下午好
Good afternoon.
谢谢你 先生Miskin
Thank you, Mr. Miskin.
现在还给你
And now back to you.
我们是否知道什么是合格的专家不得不说
Do we know what qualified experts have to say
关于休斯先生的精神影响“
about the psychiatric implications of Mr. Hughes',
呃 深居简出的行为呢？
uh, reclusive behavior?
人们可以推测...
One could speculate...
霍华德
Howard.
......在这一点上可能紧张
...possibly catatonic at this point.
似乎没有人知道
No one seems to know.
这可能有一个轴承
That could have a bearing
对很多自己的商业利益
on a lot of his business interests.
这可能会影响他的防守合约为例
It could affect his defense contracts, for example.
一长串
A long list,
包括休斯医学基金会 对不对？
including the Hughes Medical Foundation, right?
休斯赌场执照
The Hughes casino licenses
在拉斯维加斯可能会受到影响
in Las Vegas could be affected.
如果此调用不会很快在...
And if this call does not come in soon...
好吧
All right.
直升机向公众和空军军官
Helicopter to the public and Air Force officers
在卡尔弗城 加利福尼亚州
at Culver City, California.
搭载涡喷发动机 巨大的直升机设计
Powered by turbojet motors, the huge copter is designed
主要解除巨大的权重它是全球最大的飞机
primarily to lift great weights. It is the largest aircraft
- 它的种类而闻名 - 嗨
- of its kind known. - Hi.
和完善的时候 它的预期
And when perfected, it's expected
- 起飞... - 很长一段时间
- to take off... - Long time.
...随身携带一个小货车的负荷
...carry the load of a small freight car.
是啊 很长一段时间
Yeah, long time.
...百人以上该直升机本身...
...upwards of a hundred persons. The copter itself...
咦 怎么这个家伙 是吧？
Hey, how about this guy, huh?
......磅 它的旋转叶片的措施...
...pounds, and its rotating blades measure...
坦率地说 这是我的儿子 马特
Frank, this is my son, Matt.
...翻倒给小费
...from tip to tip.
嗨 Matt
Hi, Matt.
嗨
Hi.
马特 当我第一次去好莱坞
Matt, when I first went to Hollywood,
弗兰克拿起你的祖母
Frank picked up your grandmother
和我在飞机上
and me at the plane.
......在其所有的多样化和有前景的阶段飞行的未来
...future of flight in all its varied and promising phases.
我们得到了什么样的冰淇淋 莱瓦尔？
What kind of ice cream have we got, Levar?
我听到一些讲朗姆酒葡萄干
I heard some talk about rum raisin.
在这里 马特 我会告诉你
Here, Matt, I'll show you
其中朗姆酒葡萄干
where the rum raisin is.
...从亿万富翁霍华德•休斯电话
...phone call from billionaire Howard Hughes.
有座位那里 伙计们
Have a seat there, guys.
好的
Okay.
......由理查德Miskin名作家
...a writer by the name of Richard Miskin,
休斯无法记住任何东西...
that Hughes is unable to remember anything...
我跟玛米•墨菲
I talked to Mamie Murphy.
她知道理查德Miskin
She knows Richard Miskin.
霍华德可能有一些问题
Howard may have some questions.
......历史镜头拥有霍华德•休斯的...
...historical footage featuring Howard Hughes's...
这是很高兴见到你 玛拉
It's good to see you, Marla.
......在航空
...in aviation.
对我来说 太
For me, too.
40吨 57 -passenger班轮...
The 40-ton, 57 -passenger liner that...
我要让他知道你在这里
I'll let him know you're here.
......这就产生了新经大陆
...which has made a newtrans-continental,
不停的速度纪录
non-stop speed record
这里的开始
Here's the start.
...什么可能是下一个对休斯的组织
...what might be next for the Hughes organization,
如果休斯先生从来没有前进的脚步为自己辩护的权利要求
if Mr. Hughes never steps forward to defend himself against the claims
在Miskin先生的书？
in Mr. Miskin's book?
霍华德 玛拉马布里来到这里
Howard, Marla Mabrey has come here.
她说她有事情要告诉你关于Miskin
She says she has something to tell you about Miskin.
我告诉她 我会让你知道
I told her I'd let you know.
......肯定会很尴尬
...certainly going to be embarrassing
休斯和他的整个帝国
for Hughes and his entire empire.
如何解释了一个事实
How does one explain away the fact
该男子甚至不能做一个简单的电话？
that the man can't even make a simple telephone call?
带她英寸
Bring her in.
我想他们可能
I suppose they could
还拿出某种形式的其他证据
still come out with some kind of alternative evidence.
奋力其襁褓中
Struggling out of its swaddling clothes.
又是谁帮了霍华德•休斯的先驱之一
And one of the pioneers who helped was Howard Hughes,
当今业界仍然活跃
still active in the industry today.
作为一门绝技 航空速度的点...
As a stunt, the point of aviation speed...
大卫 我在看时钟
David, I'm looking at the clock
如果调用不4:30来的
and if the call doesn't come by 4:30,
那么这将是很难维护
then it will be hard to defend
霍华德•休斯对理查德Miskin的书费
Howard Hughes against the charges in Richard Miskin's book.
霍华德？
Howard?
时间在流逝 大卫
The clock is ticking, David.
你好 玛拉
Hello, Marla.
任何想法 以会发生什么？
Any thoughts as to what may happen...
我们已经失去了联系
We've lost touch.
对不起 我是
I'm sorry I was in
这种心情不好的时候 你来到拉斯维加斯
such a bad mood when you came to Las Vegas.
那是什么时候？
When was that?
五年前？
Five years ago?
我是不是在我的最好的
I was not at my best.
我知道 霍华德
I know that, Howard.
也不是一
Neither was I.
玛米•墨菲知道理查德Miskin非常好
Mamie Murphy knows Richard Miskin very well.
她告诉我 她很肯定 他从来没有见过你
She told me that she was very sure he never met you.
如果你想的话 她会作证
She'd testify if you wanted her to.
...很长的路要走朝着揭穿一个作家的说法
...go a long way towards debunking a writer's claim
他已经写了...
that he has written an...
我带着我的儿子
I came with my son.
而现在已进入什么可以被描述为...
And has now gone into what could best be described as...
打扰一下？
Excuse me?
我带着我的儿子
I came with my son.
他在客厅
He's in the living room.
而且还有另外一点是...
And there's another point to be...
而父亲呢？
And the father?
...如果休斯不
...if Hughes does not
证明他还活着 并有一些问题
prove that he's still alive, and there is some question
至于他是否
as to whether he is.
只是有人跟我拿起 它没有持续很长时间
Just someone I took up with. It didn't last long.
此次呼叫 顺便说一句
The call was, incidentally,
应该在4:00进去
supposed to come in at 4:00.
你想我来见你的儿子吗？
Would you like me to meet your son?
当然
Sure.
如果该调用想要进入
If that call were to come in
在接下来的几分钟内...
within the next several minutes...
马特？ 你想满足休斯先生？
Matt? You wanna meet Mr. Hughes?
......从纽约到纽约四天
...from New York to New York in four days.
新的航空历史是人写
New aviation history is written.
霍华德•休斯根本不容许自己
Howard Hughes simply does not allow himself
被任何人可以看到
to be seen by anyone.
霍华德 这是马特
Howard, this is Matt.
它会非常 非常难以防守霍华德•休斯
It'll be very, very difficult to defend Howard Hughes
对费...
against the charges...
问好休斯先生 马特
Say hello to Mr. Hughes, Matt.
你好
Hello.
...涵盖了他很长很长的时间由于有你
...covering him for a long, long time. As have you.
你多大了 马特？
How old are you, Matt?
四年半
Four and a half.
我很好奇 什么会成为
I'm curious as to what's going to become
帝国的他...
of the empire that he...
你看起来像我还以为你看
You look like I thought you'd look.
你也是
So do you.
为什么你在这个房间里留下来吗？
Why do you stay in this room?
你知道 我真的应该多出去
You know, I really should get out more.
好吧 弗兰克 在手机上获得了好莱坞
Okay, Frank, get Hollywood on the phone.
纳丁 得到洛杉矶 速度快
Nadine, get Los Angeles, fast.
他们还在就行了 谢了！
They're still on the line, Frank!
得到它 得到它我要做到这一点
Get it, get it. I'm going to do this.
霍华德 你可以...
Howard, you can just...
坦率地说 他们仍然就行了！
Frank, they're still on the line!
他们还在就行了？ 好
They're still on the line? Good.
马特 你要坚持一段时间了？
Matt, you wanna stick around for a while?
坦率地说 我在哪里把它？
Frank, where do I put it?
- 我这个针吗？ - 是啊
- Do I pin this on? - Yeah.
那绕着我的脖子？
That goes around my neck?
我们被告知
We are being told
我们会从霍华德•休斯立即听到
we will hear from Howard Hughes immediately.
我们正站在
We are standing by.
我想这就是我会被谈话的人
I think that's the man I'm gonna be talking to,
- 但我们会看到... - 弗兰克！
- but we'll see... - Frank!
这是属于他的 对不起
This belongs to him. I'm sorry.
马特 我就在客厅里等你
Matt, I'll wait for you in the living room.
如果你刚刚加入我们
If you just joined us,
我们一个电话待命
we're standing by for a phone call
从亿万富翁霍华德•休斯
from billionaire Howard Hughes.
我们被告知该呼叫在未来...
We've been told the call is coming in...
我听说有人自称是霍华德•休斯
I'm told someone claiming to be Howard Hughes
将随时向我们说话
will be speaking to us momentarily,
因此 我们可以评估他是否确实
so we can assess whether he is indeed
霍华德•休斯
Howard Hughes.
你在那里 休斯先生？
Are you there, Mr. Hughes?
下午好
Good afternoon.
你是哪里 先生讲？
Where are you speaking from, sir?
我从阿卡普尔科来讲
I'm speaking from Acapulco,
这是一个海港城市在格雷罗州
which is a city seaport in the state of Guerrero
墨西哥太平洋沿岸
on the Pacific coast of Mexico.
西南墨西哥城约190英里
About 190 miles southwest of Mexico City,
位于深刻的 半圆形的海湾
located on a deep, semicircular bay.
我要说的是市
I would say that the municipality
具有约一个区域
has an area of about
726.9
平方英里
square miles and
这是该州最大的城市远远大于
it is the largest city in the state. Far larger than
国有资本 奇尔潘辛戈
the state capital, Chilpancingo.
这个名字阿卡普尔科来自纳瓦特尔
The name Acapulco comes from the Nahuatl
语言它的意思是“地方大芦苇”
language. It means "place of big reeds,"
这就是我在哪里
and that is where I am.
下一个问题 谢谢
Next question, please.
基因Handsaker 美联社告诉我们一些
Gene Handsaker, Associated Press. Tell us a little
有关H-一
about the H-One.
好吧 我们先称其为“赛车”
Well, we first called it "The Racer."
它是在与迪克一起帕尔默设计由我
It was designed by me in conjunction with Dick Palmer.
我们建立它在一个小楼里
We built it in a small building
什么现在已经成为洛克希德终端
of what has now become the Lockheed terminal,
而且 顺便说一句 基因Handsaker
and that, by the way, Gene Handsaker,
是你和我第一次见面
is where you and I first met.
这架飞机载有金属机身
This airplane had a metal fuselage
其中与对接接头 我们感到非常自豪
with butt joints of which we were very proud.
它有红晕
It had flush
铆钉 后来成为了行业标准
rivets which later became standard in the industry.
它有一个木翼
It had a wooden wing
其中 当然 没有
which, of course, did not
成为标准的 但它是唯一
become standard, but it was the only thing
在拥有的时候
at the time that had
光滑的表面 我们需要正如我所说
the smooth surface that we needed. As I say,
一个引擎
a single engine,
单座飞机 一个美丽的小东西
single-seat airplane, a beautiful little thing.
我仍然有它 其实
I still have it, actually,
出在出厂时卡尔弗城
out at the factory at Culver City.
你应该去那里 基因
You should go out there sometime, Gene,
看一看吧下一个问题 谢谢
and take a look at it. Next question, please.
格拉德温山 为纽约时报
Gladwin Hill, for The New York Times.
我如何知道你 休斯先生
How well I know you, Mr. Hughes.
如何以及你知道这本书的作者 理查德Miskin？
How well do you know the book's writer, Richard Miskin?
我不认识他
I don't know him.
我从来没有见过他我从来没有听说过他
I've never seen him. I've never even heard of him
直到前两天
until two days ago.
嗨 霍华德弗农•斯科特在这里
Hi, Howard. Vernon Scott here.
只要你开始说话 我知道这是霍华德•休斯
As soon as you started to talk, I knew it was Howard Hughes.
难道你真的穿网球鞋
Did you really wear tennis shoes
与你的晚礼服？
with your tuxedo?
是啊 他们的鞋制成
Yeah, well, they were shoes made of
排序非战略物资
sort of a non-strategic material.
帆布或人造皮革的种类
Kind of a canvas or imitation leather.
我有一双这样的 我非常喜欢
I had a pair of these that I liked very much.
我会穿他们 然后他们...
I would wear them, and then they...
有些人叫他们的网球鞋 但是我...
Some people called them tennis shoes, but I...
我不认为他们有什么关系正对一个网球场
I don't think they had anything to do with being on a tennis court.
我能问你几个问题
Can I ask you a couple of questions
涉及国家安全？
relating to national security?
哦 我不这么认为
Oh, I don't think so.
你知道 我不在乎经常出现在公众面前 但是...
You know, I don't care to appear in public very often, but...
我真的应该多出去走走
I really should get out more.
但它是一个很高兴和你说话 先生们
But it has been a pleasure speaking to you, gentlemen.
任何时候 晚上好
Any time. Good evening.
我认为总结
I think that concludes
我们的新闻发布会 谢谢
our press conference. Thank you,
休斯先生
Mr. Hughes.
我认为有与他手中的问题出版商
I think there's a publisher with a problem on his hands.
你是真的好
You were really good.
我要去找我妈妈 再见
I have to go find my mom. Bye.
孩子！孩子！
Kid! Kid!
孩子？
Kid?
事情仰视 弗兰克
Things are looking up, Frank.
你做得不错
You did good.
我们又回到了好莱坞
We're going back to Hollywood.
我感觉很好！
I feel good!
我想 是时候回家了！ 你懂...
I think it's time to go home! You know...
霍华德...
Howard...
你已经做了很多伟大的事情
You've done a lot of great things,
你已经做了很多伟大的事情对我来说
and you've done a lot of great things for me.
我觉得是时候让你回家
I think it is time for you to go home.
而且我认为是时候让我继续前进
And I think it's time for me to move on.
什么？
What?
我辞职 霍华德
I'm quitting, Howard.
他们去哪了？
Where'd they go?
他们还挺溜了出去
They kinda slipped out.
保持对他的眼睛 莱瓦尔
Keep an eye on him, Levar.
坦率？
Frank?
你认为这是一次我们试一试？
You think it's time we give it a try?
让我们马特
Let's get Matt.
嘿 你知道吗？ 我有一个很好的主意！
Hey, you know what? I got a really good idea!
是什么在这些瓶子？
What's in those bottles?
这是水
That's water.
从缅因州
From Maine.
水
Water.
从缅因州
From Maine.
♪他想了一下♪
♪ He thought for a moment ♪
♪然后他回答♪
♪ Then he answered ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用于你♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply to you ♪
♪他说 很简单地 静静地过♪
♪ He said it very simply and quietly too ♪
♪不过好像有没有任何疑问 在所有他知道♪
♪ But as if there wasn't any doubt at all that he knew ♪
♪他给我的礼物 我会珍惜♪
♪ He gave me a gift that I would treasure ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用于你♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply to you ♪
♪在我们看到的电影♪
♪ In the movies we see ♪
♪在电视上的节目♪
♪ In the shows on TV ♪
♪而在国歌热情演唱♪
♪ And in anthems passionately sung ♪
♪有 你有一个消息♪
♪ There's a message that you've got ♪
♪为了让自己相信♪
♪ To keep believing in yourself ♪
♪但他们通常是指如果你还年轻♪
♪ But they generally mean if you're young ♪
♪是它写在空中 因为它似乎是♪
♪ Is it written in the air as it seems to be ♪
♪我们还没有长都找到我们的命运♪
♪ That we haven't long at all to find our destiny ♪
♪我会永远记得感恩♪
♪ I'll always remember to be grateful ♪
♪这规则并不适用于我♪
♪ That the rules don't apply to me ♪
♪有一天 我告诉我的朋友♪
♪ One day I told my friend ♪
♪我是可怕的蓝色♪
♪ I was terribly blue ♪
♪是不是为时已晚做♪
♪ Was it far too late to do ♪
♪我梦见我能做什么呢？♪
♪ What I dreamed I could do? ♪
♪他想了一会儿 然后他回答♪
♪ He thought for a moment, then he answered ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用于你♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply to you ♪
♪他说 很简单地 静静地 太♪
♪ He said it very simply and quietly, too ♪
♪这仿佛根本没有什么疑问可言 他知道♪
♪ That as if there wasn't any doubt at all that he knew ♪
♪他给我的礼物 我会珍惜♪
♪ He gave me a gift that I would treasure ♪
♪他说 规则并不适用于你♪
♪ He said the rules don't apply to you ♪
♪在我们看到的电影♪
♪ In the movies we see ♪
♪在电视上的节目♪
♪ In the shows on TV ♪
♪而在国歌热情演唱♪
♪ And in anthems passionately sung ♪
♪有 你有一个消息♪
♪ There's a message that you've got ♪
♪为了让自己相信♪
♪ To keep believing in yourself ♪
♪但他们通常是指如果你还年轻♪
♪ But they generally mean if you're young ♪
♪是它写在空中 因为它似乎是♪
♪ Is it written in the air as it seems to be ♪
♪那我们的避风港'T长途都找到我们的命运♪
♪ That we haven 't long at all to find our destiny ♪
♪我会永远记得感恩♪
♪ I'll always remember to be grateful ♪
♪这规则并不适用于我♪
♪ That the rules don't apply to me ♪
♪我不会骗♪
♪ I wouldn't lie ♪
♪的规则并不适用♪
♪ The rules don't apply ♪
♪要你♪
♪ To you ♪